To my brother Mehmet, who always
wanted me to shoot a Turkish film.
Groaning melodies entered into my soul.
Such a dream is a place of eternal songs.
Singers and
loving people everywhere.
The music world is like
dreams, like an own world.
Everybody wants to become a singer, wants
to get famous and honoured, but...
...all people are waiting for agenerous
stranger, for a saving angel, who...
...is taking them by hand.
They are waiting for us.
Hear, the time has come.
As there are policemen in civil...
...there are angels in civil, who are
living here.
this film was inspired by true stories
They have composed songs, even
have asked for help.
A visit without invitation is not
suitable for the race...
of angels that much caprice is necessary.
Properly everything there
is like a movie.
If you are open for such things, it will be
impossible to you...
...to distinguish reality of movie...
It is like a tale.
Everywhere evil wolfs are leering.
Well, there is Seyfi...
...he is the leader of the group. He is an
artist, who knows his profession:
The first setting of the movie is the most
important one.
If this is correct your spectator will be
bound.
His glance will be tied
like the eyes of a duck
...that is looking at a fish.
Like a confused duck.
The main point of shooting
is the position of the camera.
Give it to me! Hurry up, we want to
record right now.
Move don't look like fishes, who have
seen a duck! Music!
What kind of music? Do you have
something to do with music?
I was a fan of Elvis.
In former days I listened to jazz.
When I was in love...
...I liked Arabic music and than rock.
I prefer arrangements, like flowers.
Now treason and injustice reign the
music world.
Good people exist only in tales.
An example: love had robbed all reason
of Melih...
...a promising young singer.
He also was one of these people...
...who would sacrifice
everything for love.
Who is left will be my haul.
Where is my red-brown crane?
Why didn't you get changed?
I will not act. I have come in order to collect
my luggage.
Where to? With this guy?
Didn't I say you, that he is not allowed to
show himself at this place?
Get away you!
That's the reason, that he is waiting outside.
Tayyar, I have to get money still!
First the scene, than the money!
Where can I find a singer still?
I am pregnant. I need the money.
What, you are pregnant?
No stage to ya no more Melih! You'll
sing in bath houses only!
Don't cry so loudly! You don't know
anything!
Give me the money, you arse-hole!
You can't call a Lacen an arse-hole
without loosing your life...
Why without consequences?
The angels are surrounding her but
sometimes unexpected things happen.
Suddenly all doors had been closed to them.
They didn't see any exit.
An awkward love-fairy
There was this nice saying
played a bad game with these lost souls.
They all fall together, if one of
them is falling.
We couldn't permit it.
Did somebody make promises?
The financial decisions have been
made at the last meeting.
- That's not important.
- With whom has been arranged this?
Mister Orhan,
a genius in financing. Specialist for legal
contracts.
He has succeeded to make a warm
refuge of a tiny hotel-room.
One is appealing for prayer. Please get up!
The prayer, Orhan Abi!
Hoca would like it to have a talk with
you. The debts are towering up.
He is downstairs and seems to
be very upset.
Okay, therefore I have woken up early.
After the prayer I wanted...
You didn't still sign a contract, did you?
He have made an usual agreement
with the producer.
Hayri Bey is a remarkable head.
He is really charismatic.
He is worried about his artists
like a protecting fairy.
They will come soon.
Oh god, let it go well!
Stop it, so early in the morning!
Let me go to the W.C, you son of a bitch!
It is not easy, to produce music.
Mister Hayri feels a peculiar pleasure
at the meal of the wolfs.
They find a diamant in the mud.
His career has begun in Europe.
He advanced quickly.
Now we are at Love!
Sure, a honourable boy, but a certain
distance is necessary.
A real cuddle-cat!
Come and applaud also!
Enough! Pigs!
St, the boss is calling!
You are terrific, applaud with us!
- Hello, I am Sansar.
- I know you.
Tonight there will be a Turkish night in
Munich.
I would like to be the star on the stage
in stead of Erdil.
- Don't you havea manager?
- No.
Such a coincidence!
You have to sign here! In Germany
nothing works without contract.
Whom do I see?
Coming all the way to here!
- He is it!- Friends, we have to interrupt
the meeting. There is a visitor.
Welcome.
Please be quite, madam Firuze.
Excuse me, can we have a talk outside?
This person is seeking me everywhere!
# Stay, where you are
# Don't make me crazy
# I haven't to pay a bill
# neither have I to go to confession
# I don't see my left hand, not my right hand
# I can't separate friends of enemies
# I don't know myself anymore.
I capitulate and stop the game
- How are you, Hayri?
- Wow! Is there somebody at the door?
See you!
You damned... That's my house.
You can't exchange the lock!
Asshole!
Please, open the door.
- Otherwise I will break it open!
- Shut up!
Don't shout! Open that damned door!
I only want to Change my clothes and
will go again immediately.
Show me the children!
You have forgotten, how our children
look like.
- I am getting crazy! That's my house!
- The bum of that bitch is your home.
Your companions are not able also to
maintain their wives.
I look after the woman here.
I will say to Seyfi, that he has to pick up me.
We have discovered a new voice.
The boy is great.
A voice like candy. The new Pavarotti.
We will make studio-sessions today.
Not with the same clothes.
Neval, I will dedicate you the album.
- Piss off!
- What is the matter, Neval?
- Hamit!
- Good morning.
- How are you, my love?
- Good, but I hardly can hear you.
- Take off your headphones!
- I don't hear anything.
Regard this face, this attitude. The people
will close him in their hearts.
The people will close me in their hearts.
- Hopefully everything is going well today.
- Thanks.
- I would wish, that you will stay modest
always. Okay? -I will not Change.
- No, not at all. What's the matter with
the basis? -Everything is clear:
the violins and the percussion. -Did
the scoundrels play well? -Excellent!
Come with us. Welcome on the market
of records, Hamit.
Look around very well.
Here is the real battle-field.
If you enter here by foot, your heart
will beat wildly.
- What is that? - A pump.
- A natural injection.
- A natural injection-pump. -That's why you
have to appear here with a safe tank
so that the rifles of the infantry immediately.
Hayri, do you know, which datum we have?
- You have to talk with him.
- But he is totally silly already.
- What do you drink?
- Medicine for nightingales.
- What is this supposed to be?
- It makes singing every silent nightingale.
Hayri wants studio-fee.
I hardly could Change his mind.
- Let's work now.
- Thanks.
Music.
The tape has a rotation-problem. It is turning
round too quickly.
- No, Ahmet Bey did want this way.
- Who is Ahmet Bey?
And we have been in accordance of his
wishes. Several times we have said to him.
- One moment, dear Ahmet.
- Yes, please?
You know, that the record has cost the
whole money. The musicians have arrived.
The pit is in a way too sharp.
How do you mean being able to sing this?
- I have prepared explicitly B-flat. I am tenor.
- What?
B- flat.
Hayri, I am the king.
Well, we will see!
You and B-flat, you fucked nightingale!
The A is better for you.
- We have to edit it.
- Go away with lukewarm water.
No, I mean the cassette tape. But how
and with whom?
- We have to find somebody, Hayri?
- What?
So we went to bottom totally.
- Is not there a fish, that is living at the bottom? What is his name?
- How can I know it?
Such a flat one with prickles on his tail.
I know, that poisonous one.
He serves electric shocks. We are like them.
We are laying in the sand and waiting
noiseless.
Suddenly we attack.
No, we don't want to get a shock.
Look, if the tape of Ýbrahim Tatlýses doesn't
arrive, could...
...you give him back the box and
request your money?
We are not able to sell it. We are
still sitting on it.
Friends, the music-family of Umut remotes the
word repayment out of his vocabulary right now.
- Our possibilities for retaking are tired out.
- What does it mean?
It is limited at 30%, but we haven't even
made al 50% of the music-box.
Go, my friend!
Go, my friend.
Ýbrahim's bull!
That's the matter, master?
Who is coming there? Welcome, my dear!
I just have said to the boys,
that Ibrahim is looking like Elvis very
much! Haven't I, Orhan? -Yes, you have.
Orhan, my dear, you have sold the not
existing tape except to me to otherpeople.
Orhan, coffee. That are all rumours!
You are our marketing man.
Oh no! How do you want to pay?
Well, this new boy, what was his name? He
is tenor, singing B-flat, believe me!
What does B-flat mean? Could you sell
his last tape?
Not at all! Nothing happened.
We have made 15000 records of his last
box but we had to retake 25000.
Even the boxes of the black market had
been burdened to us.
Tayyar, my sir, we just have
spoken about you.
Twenty days?
That never will be sufficient! Say it to me, if I
make a mistake.
Your debts amount to 88.000 $
I beg you, say at least twenty days!
Say it to me, if I make a mistake.
What will we do, Hayri?
We will go to sleep three times and will
wake up three times.
After three days we will get our
money or not?
What will be now? Boxes mean money.
We let sing somebody, but whom?
Well, I get a little bit money...
...of the last box. I have thought: if it is
convenient now...
Hayri?
Orhan?
Why do you laugh?
You have broken the nose of
a new singer!
- No, I don't have people for you.
- This Sansar was not able to sing the song.
One can't beat up all people
who are not able to sing.
In short time you would have a
slaughterhouse.
Honoured audience, the unique national
634th competition...
...for the golden dream presents participant
number 42: Semra Comez!
- We have no other merchandise for you.
- Sansar,
we want this boy from Germany.
No, if I bring him here, he may have
money...
...that will land in your pocket.
You will produce
the box for good money...
...and my fee will be a watch.
No, my love, I can't do anything for you.
Ferhat, that you had to call me.
I was not present just at the moment, you
wanted to telephone me.
Something is wrong with the international
connections. I could not reach you.
How is the weather in Germany?
Well, my friends tell me that I look very
well, but you might have your own opinion.
Please? No, my eyebrows did not grow
together...
...but if you want, I can let them grow.
That's what they do themselves already.
Therefor I meant... rap, pop, jazz, I could
sing everything.
Ferhat, sing something!
In B-flat please!
That's a serious supply for a box, isn't it?
# I am a male old maid
# There is no wife for
lazy-bones
# What can we make still?
# I am not able to rob a bank
# In that way I have come to love
# My love is totally different
# I have seen so many beautiful girls.
The whole day
# Men do suffer also and not so little
# but this is no solution. Only the matrimony
gives purification
Ýbrahim, my record-master has to come and
edit my box...
...otherwise I will suicide.
Make for me a box! Than I will
become famous.
Hear, daddy, let me explain. Please, let me
explain it.
Tayyar sends you his greetings.
Stop! Nothing may be wrong left or right?
Where is Umut-music, please?
Left.
Oh, my god! They kill!
Allah, Allah!
- Master, they have killed somebody inside.
- All life will be taste dead. - What?
- They have shot Ibrahim!
- Salvation to your soul, Ýbrahim!
- They have hit his heel only! -Could you
save your life again, you dirty swine!
- Where is Umut-music?
- Look over there.
But in reality there is no hope and no music.
If you can wait, you may meet her.
I repeat, we will pay. Orhan, do something!
I can't do anything, I am standing
between two liquidations.
Hayri, let it be! Let it be their blame!
Forget it!
Let me the little T.V. please. Tomorrow
comes an international game. Osman!
You are on my black list, because you
have done this to me.
Cancel that list, man!
Rather pay your debts.
- Hayri!
- Good recovery, my dear Ibrahim!
- That has nothing to do with us.
You have still two days, do you understand?
I am lost. They take even the fax.
Please not! Be pity!
Please not! Not the fax!
You can take evrything, everything!
They will kill me,if they discover, that I have
bought it in a second hand shop.
How much did you pay for it, my little boy?
What kind of money? I have paid with
natural products.
Three parcels with dance-music!
Your name should be engraved in the
monument for the resurrected people.
Your are such a fox!
What do you say? The inner of the
TV was empty.
I have put a sewing-machine in it in order to
make it heavier.
- Really?
- Pardon, who is Mister Hayri?
- He has died, I regret.
- How?
- His mortal remains are
washed. - Has he died? - Yes.
What do you say there? It is for him, that
I have made such a long voyage.
- Who is seeking him?
- Ferhat Can from Germany.
My hero, dear brother, Hayri!
Welcome, you well-looking star.
Let us beat the record at the record-market.
Orhan,
call for the notary in order to make a
protocol.
A record in short time producing of
music-boxes!
Orhan, call now for the studio in
order to record.
Not now, it is closed. To-morrow.
OK, OK, to-morrow.
So you have time for learning the songs.
Everything here in Istanbul goes fast.
- There is my partner Orhan.
Where is Seyfi? - Hello!
Clip PR-leader Seyfi. You know already
our star Melih.
Well, that TV...
Do make something. Well, we were busy,
we wanted to renew the decorations...
...and than you came. Excuse me for the
disorder.
Come to here. This here and this.
- Is it ready?
- Yes, ready. That is it!
What kind of market is this? I thought,
you were dead.
God save us! He might give us all a long life.
Ferhat there is this fish, that is hiding
under the sand.
If you step on him he offers you an
electric shock.
That's what I want to ask you the whole
time, but I am forgetting it ever.
We are exactly like this fisch.
We will strike, Melih.
Bring him to Kahtalý in order to tidy up.
With this hair he has no chance.
Let us cut it.
This boy will become very famous.
We will strike.
It will come a day, that we enter this hotel
with pride and high breast.
That is it! Tatu Head&Leg is
presenting proudly.
- Do you need something more?
- Bring another bottle. Will we drink it?
Delicious. I haven't eaten it since
three months.
- Orhan, what did we properly sign today?
- A contract.
Sansar let me sign something also.
Let me see!
Miss Sansar is really okay.
We make charges and PR and she gets
the whipped cream.
It does go like that! Here is a paragraph, that
binds you ten years at us.
- What, ten years?
- Well, than good luck!
What do you think?
Last five years I am not able to think of other
things than of music.
Sometimes your look is darkling.
Nevertheless you are going on. Than you
look back and you see,
that you are at the same place.
You are not there.
- Hopefully this room will bring you
good luck. - Hopefully.
It didn't bring me luck, but I am content,
when I am in love.
We are artists. We are living of air and love.
I repeat it many times. This boy is so
sensitive.
I beg you pardon, my nerves!
- Because you have said...
- Boy to a full-grown man.
- What is the connection with your baby?
- High blood pressure.
It would be better, if she doesn't
get her baby.
The results of the medical
examination are bad.
That is the revenge of the sensitive people.
We are lost.
Does somebody come with me
into the night-bar?
# There is no kind of sorrows, that I don't
know, that I didn't suffer
# No day, no night without grief
After the black-out of current he jumped
to the stage.
He has a good voice but no reason. Right
away he has contacted Tayyar.
- Who is Tayyar?
- Come, my egg, please come!
Hayri, you have brought bad
luck to this girl!
The one, who let shoot in the foot of
Ýbrahim, is Tayyar
- Why did he do it?
- Main point is...
...the length of the prick, do you understand?
We have found a job at Kumkapý.
Tayyar has forbidden Melih, to go on stage.
He let shoot in the leg of the operator
of the club.
But why got Melih upset?
Tayyar has fallen in love with Melih's girl.
That the reason, why his behaviour is gentle.
# There is no trace of my old ego
# I am tired of the pains
# Please support my arms.
Otherwise I will fall down
# I am so lonesome and lonely
Why don't you tell this guy, that you are
pregnant?
He doesn't know, if he will marry me.
There is still time.
What ever will happen, I will give
birth to this baby.
First time of my life I am doing
something useful.
Let us say, that we tolerate these men
because of their victorious future.
If their luck has turned and the money is
flowing...
...they will leave us.
The truth is, girls, that there are only roles
for men in this picture.
What will happen with us?
My dear god, why did you create these
women?
# I don't like it any more
# To be playthings!
# Am I a slave?
# So delivered I am tired of life
# She can go, if she doesn't need
me any more
# Give me patience...
Here is the real battle-field.
We will win.
Kahtalý! We will record.
He is really a nighintale.
My hero, my best one!
Did I succeed?
- Do I have a box also?
- Come and let me kiss you! Well made!
What have I said you?
This boy will belong to the very grand
people, I promise.
What is the matter here?
We have discovered him and you will pick
him up! No sir!
Didn't you want to come to me directly
after your arrival?
Don't exaggerate it, Sansar!
The last one, you have served us, was suited
to nothing. Thereafter we took that one.
To where, what is the matter? No, there is
nothing, to where do you go?
One minute.
Here is a copy of the contract and
what do we read?
Ferhat Can, living at Berlin,
Neuköllnstr. 62.
Bravo, you gained the rights.
The German judges will worry about them.
Well, perhaps it will make sense,
if you ask my advice...
...before making the next contract, Sansar.
This here has not ended!
There comes an aftermath.
Sansar, will never forget this.
She will not forget it! She is an elephant.
What, twenty?
In spite of your debts I have to spend
my own money for...
...t Do you have more wishes? s?
You have to trust me, Osman!
You know, my name means confidence.
What kind of confidence?
The loss of your TV by decision
of the court?
Japanese technology is great.
Look, the new mobile phone is...
...a flat-iron at the same time.
- Really?
We will buy it for your wife.
# Don't trust him with your love
# He will transform your tears to ferocious
streams
# Thanks to men your laughing will become
weeping
# Don't be deceived by him, don't
believe him
# He will leave you and will
speak about you
# He will leave you and will speak
about you
Stop it!
The face of the black man is too dark!
Good! But what will we do?
With more light she will look shabby,
with less light...
...the black dancer will be in darkness.
What can we do?
How do the Americans succeed?
They have black, red, white and mixed
people?
The Americans do know their business.
So Tanju Gürsoy doesn't want to
participate on our program.
You don't still have the demo of that boy.
He also looks very well. Could you
take charge of him?
I will give birth to this child, whatever it will
cost me.
You will guard me and my child.
Muammer!
What the hell is this?
Sterling from North-Africa!
In which pocket can I put this stuff?
It has been written in the contract, that the
rent is paid in foreign currency.
Well, that is exactly what we are doing.
In the exchange office they have regarded the card,
but didn't even find the name of the country, my child.
Surely it was an obsolete card.
Now they have new ones, after civil war...
...many people have died. Didn't you
hear about it?
They have gold-leads.
Look, the nephew of this king has given
us the money personally.
We make a box for his nephew. Heaven,
what a voice!
- A nightingale!
- Heaven, we will become rich.
I have enough of you. You have to leave
this shop immediately, understood?
Run!
If we don't organise money for the...
...advertisements of the box, we will be lost.
Do you call it black money?
# My breath suffices to say it
# but what, if you don't listen to me?
# I have come in order to proceed
through the sea of love
# and to plunge into your ocean
# I am the better creature of god
# have no bad veins
# I am the nightingale of these company
# I have come to you in order to sing for you
# My deficit is my kernel
# I have come for living in your home
Hayri! Osman didn't make the boxes!Shit!
Osman, you breach of promise!
I will kill you! Go away!
Hayri, I beg you, stop it!
You got that much money. Don't you
have any conscience?
I beg you pardon, take it as repayment
of your former debts.
Without a brother like you I would do
much better!
And you, brother? Because of you
I was even in prison!
Only one week! There are people who
use to die for their brothers.
You kill your brother with your own hands!
- If mother would be still alive, she would
spit you in your face! -Mama!
- What do you say there, are you crazy?
- Let the family out of game.
You have blamed us enough already.
Gods punishment will strike you!
- Damned the day, where on I became your
brother! -It is you, who should be damned!
- I said it first! - Damned!
- I took green.
- 572 €
- Is the plot inclusive?
I am so sorry, but
the medicines from Germany are
transported in...
...little condensers. Therefore they are a
little bit expensive!
I have to stay culpable for the half.
How much is an €, most honoured man?
I say hello!
- Looks great!
- Money!
Look at him!
"Nice clothes. Take them off. Come with
me to my home".
- Hayri!
- Already one time more! Come separate!
We have been saved!
Didn't I say you, that I will take revenge for
you and Neval.
This day has come.
- What do you say there?
- Didn't Tanju Gürsoy cancel?
Therefore they bring out young talents.
I have given the demo to the
stage-assistent.
I have said, that he possesses
evening-clothes also.
Well. But Osman didn't make the boxes
if Ýbrahim hears it, he will make us to
ground meat!
If Ferhat wins the friendship of
Ýbrahim at TV?
If he says, that he has supported him?
In that case we will be saved?
Promotion, TV, I got you, Ýbrahim!
- Come, go now! When is the broadcasting?
- It is urgent, immediately!
Do you have your clothes with you?
- Well, I used the money of the
advertisements for... - OK, Melih,
go quickly to the hotel and take it.
Well Orhan, let us tell it Ýbrahim
"Nice clothes. Take them off. Baby,
come with me to my home. "
Hear, give me the key of Ferhat's
hotelroom!
I really thought, it was the old uncle,
Isn't that Ferhat's stage-costume,
that you wear?
Right. Exactly!
- What did you do?
- I modified it. It will be my stage-costume...
Oh, no! What did you do?
Ferhat, how are you looking?
What is the matter?
Seyfi, the studio is waiting for you.
Go! Hurry up!
The humorists to this side and the
singers to the other one.
Say: "My biography has begun very sad.
Everybody died already, when
I was still very little"
- Improvise something!
- And if it will come to light later?
Than you can say, that they have
died for you.
Don't forget, to bring the audience to
applause...
...move your head a little bit to the right at
the beginning of the song!
- Go! - We come! Give him the stuff
afterward, when he goes.
- What stuff?
- Not before the end of singing.
You wait here and than you will
be called in series.
- She is really like an angel.
- Her name is Melek
- That's not true!
- It is. You are in love, don't you?
I am dying, man!
Look Ferhat, when the red light is burning...
...the camera will be pointed at you, okay?
- Regard my artists!
Hello, make everything well. They are my
artists!
Don't take me with you as if I were a
pimp.
How often I did explain it to you?
My car was defect.
You didn't do me a pleasure. Besides we
haven't made an agreement,
that you would come to me in my home.
But it has happened. So I can see,
where you are living.
- Can I do something goods to you?
- What do you mean?
- Will I give you the telephone-number?
- Of whom?
Okay, let me do it!
I love fashion shows.
The only thing, that I don't like, are the
clothes.
Underwear is not the worst thing.
- Nature would be better.
- Hayri?
- Yes, my dear? -Do you know, why she
has shot me in my foot?
I know, it handled of the prick-length.
- Ss!
- What? What did you say?
- Why?
-20000 Hayri!
I want the boxes and the money.
To-morrow is deadline.
You will be amazed, they will bring our new
boy now instead of...
...Tanju Gürsoy, isn't it, Orhan?
- Solo, solo!
Money!
Damned, in spite of my illness they brought
me to here! I am there!
Welcome.
Don't smile to me like a queen
of wines, my child.
Look, I have come to here in spite of illness
without bribery I will not act.
Now we are sitting in the shit!
Sorry, we have to modify the broadcast.
Well, next time better!
- Oh, no!
- In this way it will not go. Go now!
Welcome, dear spectators at the screen.
You do know him from his pictures,
his songs,
his private style of life and his
terrific shows.
Bravo, thist time you have founf somebody,
who is really good.
- I have notion of talents.
- For you: Tanju Gürsoy!
Your whole life is a lie!
So I came in spite ofillness.
I was longing for my fans.
Welcome. Straight on:
One is asking if there is silicon in this
terrific body?
In my boby everything is natural. As I said
already:
I am totally content about myself.
Isn't this answer worth for an applause?
One knows her because of her famous days.
But how were the years at the conservatory?
Surely, the voice has become
a little bit worse.
Education is very important.
I have learned at two universities.
I studied at the medical faculty of Çapa.
Neuro-psychology.
After some years at the university I was
snared by my passion for music.
We have had good, important teachers.
We were taught loving, important...
...pots boiling with love and passion.
My teacher brought me into a concert.
After some vocal problems of the soloist
he threw me on the stage!
What is this?
Is it a joke?
Do you see it!
My artist is at T.V.!
He is the coming star on the market.
- My name is Ferhat.
- Very fine.
- My family-name is Can.
- What did he say?
He still didn't say anything!
We have made an album for Umut Müzik
with friends.
He said Umut Müzik!
The album is called "Flowerfields".
What happened? The current!
He did want to thank you at this way:
"We are editing the box thanks Ýbrahim"
Bring the generator!
If you ask me now, what music means, so...
Let us ask, otherwise he will die by
excitement.
Well, music means to me a beautiful woman,
as beautiful as you.
I go to bed with her and wake up with her.
I wish you a good broadcast. What is this,
where is Art staying?
That is more like a erotic broadcast. Say,
there is a woman in me.
Ask and give the answer yourself. What am I
seeking here?
That's Tanju Gürsoy!
You never know, how you are.
But if you would ask me, what Art is...
Do you ask me, what Art is?
Is there a generator?
In my opinion Art is a deal with the
spectator.
Properly all spectators are like one person.
You force them to listen and imagine,
that one of them at the screen is
recording you.
That is trade!
Now I have got the idea,
that I want to remember me to Ibrahim,
who truly accompanied me on these journey.
We thank you for this interesting
conversation and
continue our broadcast according
to the program.
There is a pause for advertising, but first...
# I was naiv and had been deceived
by the colour of the world
# I trusted a dream and was
despaired in vain
# I believed you would be mine for all times
# I am dying, beloved, and
you are my poison
# You were the first man in my life:
now you are the last
A generator, man! I give the Umut
music empire for a generator!
# I am a poor maiden, didn't do any
evil in this world
# I have established me in your
neighbourhood
# I never have confessed my love to
somebody
You are there still. What a scandal!
My poor heart!
Three minutes pause for advertising.
We are in advertising, 3.40.
# You are my centre and my cover
# My past and my last
Didn't we want to strike like that fish!
If there comes a storm, the fishes
will strike us.
Oh, if we could die now! We would be
free of this damned world!
Why don't you open it?
What do you make there?
- Here, the suicide-letter.
- Do you write often?
When inspiration comes,
sometimes.
- Read it to me!
- No, no! It is to absurd.
Well, read it!
- This is the suicide-letter of an
still existing Ferhat. -Go on!
Nobody is responsiblefor my death,
Ferhat Can.
- Hayri!
- This is not a despairing act.
- Really not? - Never before in my life
I felt so courageous.
I was in love with songs
I hope my tape will be published.
And my lifeless voice will be at stores.
This is my wish from Umut Music.
My soul will be with you.
Goodbye cruel world.
Goodbye.
Umut Müzik means everything for us.
Tomorrow it will be on all front pages.
All people will be baffled.
The letter is a poem. If this box will not be
sold like warm rolls, I let cut...
...my prick and become Hayriye.
Ferhat Can, represented by
Umut Music, stops with...
...the stolen car on the Bosporus bridge.
When he is holding his poetic...
...last letter in his hands, the camera
glides down very slowly...
...and falls. In this moment your song
begins, okay? -Everything is clear.
Some more effects...
...tears, a sincere, but bitter
smile on his face.
Than we will have succeeded.
- Who is playing too?
- Principe: best friend. Melih,...
You could play his role. Cry! Don't cry too
modestly.
You will return three months later. "Ferhat
Can, the box of Abi's ghost. "
Geistes Abi" It will be a big seller.
Thereafter we will celebrate in Russia.
- Did you sign the letter?
- What now?
The reader has to know, that it was you,
who had died.
I wrote it at the head of the letter.
There it is. It has be signed also. Even the
stamp of Umut Music has been given.
Bravo, well thought.
That is the wrong car! The letter ought
to be in the other car!
# Turkey Turkey you're a lovely country
# Turkey Turkey you're a cozy land.
# You're the land of chiskebab and raki
# You're the place of living I have planed
# Places full of very friendly people
# Always trying to help you if they can
# Turkey Turkey Turkey I adore you
# Turkey Turkey Turkey I love you
Ýbrahim? Hayri.
Let's make it short.
We were not able to organise money.
We are in the mud. We can't move us
above zero.
Two posters for 88000 $ 2 and one DAT.
Wonderful.
You want to cut out us?
What's on the box, that I could share?
If there is no other way to reach your mind:
we will send the bill and get the
money one day later.
There is no other way!
- Hello, Kaveci.
- How are you, daddy?
My foot?
Well, it sends you his greetings.
I did mind the bones. Good recovery!
Excuse for the circumstances. We are
mediators.
Of course, whatever you want.
Is it the bill, Hayri?
Enough! We don't chop off!
What does this mean?
We have to take the problem at the roots.
- Umut Music?
- Upstairs.
All people have their story. This one
will be our story.
Hello?
- Don't make humbug. Don't cause costs,
Hayri. - Say goodbye to my children.
- Umut Music, right?
- Yes?
I would like to buy a box
of Ferhat Can.
- In the moment we have no more boxes.
- And he?
- Who?
- Ferhat Can?
We don't have him either.
Probably he is walking
around a little.
- I hope, I didn't disturb your work.
- Not at all!
Go on, dear sirs, didn't you see something
like that never before?
We all are artists.
Kahtalý? Don't call the police!
It was the wrong shop. They thought,
it was Osman's one
and shot it.
- Go, go! - Where do you stay?
This lady is waiting for you.
He was in the hotel.
- Hello. I am Firuze.
- And I Ferhat.
Excuse me, there was a little accident.
Fortunately you haven't been injured.
Such a jewel as you are!
One should preserve you in worthy safes.
You have called me and I have come.
I am this person, who is pursuing you with
attentiveness.
I would like to have your box.
As you said: the selling has begin.
Are there boxes?
- Ferhat Bey, would you sing for me one
time more? - Of course.
What was it? " Come back "
is a beautiful song.
- Flowerfields.
- Really a beautiful song.
- Ferhats box is not ready.
- We have a momentary financial problem.
But mister Melih has beautiful boxes.
Thank you very much.
I would like to invest in you.
What do you mean?
I am well to do. My husband and I were
long times active for Art,
of course as dilettantes.
- Wonderful.
- Music is very important to me.
- And to your husband?
I lost him three years ago. Cancer.
My condolence...
What kind of cancer?
Heart-cancer, that means money.
Children, go out a moment.
I want to have a talk with this lady.
I wish, that mister Ferhat Bey
stays, please.
Of course he has to stay. I meaned...
There is no reason for secrets.
Ask for tea, if you want.
Our most urgent problem.
The financial problem can be solved easily.
Here is the bank.
We call for the director.
Hello, mister Altan.
Thank you.
Please, open for me an account,
favouring Ferhat Can.
He will be disposable to you for
informations. Speak!
Hello?
- Mother's name?
- Sýdýka.
- Father's name?
- Sinan.
- Where's your born?
- Ankara.
- Yours birth date?
- 76
Can I speak Miss Sýdýka again?
Thank you.
I want, that you will look very distinguished.
Hello Vakko?
Please write down his name:
Ferhat Can!
He comes to you for shopping.
Put everything on my meine account.
Thanks.
- Besides it looks untidily here. You have to
do something. -That is condition.
If you will make me happy, I will revenge me.
Do, what I say. The rest comes alone.
Main point you believe. See you soon!
Next time Secen will come with me.
She is able to give tips to you.
- Sezen?
- Sezen Aksu.
She was a narrow friend of my late husband.
- Once she composed a song for me.
- FÝRUZEE!...
Yes, I was very popular.
Well, it was a pleasure to me, mister Ferhat.
- So to us, at any case.
- Ferhat will accompany you until your car!
Of course.
Don't forget: The beginning is the half
business.
The end is the other half.
If you want to kill yourself, do it by living.
- And where do you live?
- In an hotel, in cartoon.
Hotel Cartoon? Understand.
Hotels
ever give a bad feeling.
The sorrows and pains of the guests use
to remain in the rooms.
- Rent a house.
- Okay.
On the backside of the mosque you will find
"Home Immoveables".
Remember me to mister Sadettin. He will
take sorrow for the house.
- Thank you very much, why do you do that?
- What?
Why do you help us?
You has called me and I have come.
You will get a cold in this weather.
- That's not important. -I have sent
away my driver. I will take a taxi.
I will call for a taxi.
Please wait. I will tell you something.
I didn't drive by bus since school-time.
You would take a city-bus?
Do you see, that you too have influence.
I have been changed by you.
Nevertheless you should not claim
this too much.
Please what?
The human being doesn't register
his own life.
He has to learn, how to live. See you soon.
Hello.
What are you doing. Bring the things
downstairs!
We have counted the days also.
We will pay you cash...
I don't want it!
This debt-story has no end.
We will edit your box also.
- Which box?
- That one with the prayers.
The angels came down from heaven, so
pure.
- No prayer for the soul. Hymns with
prayers!- That is also beautiful.
I get goose-flesh, Hayri.
Cut off! You are producing boxes
for bitches in order to...
...mix them with my prayer-hymns.
I don't want a box!
We of Umut Music will renew the
structures of our company.
If we bring out your prayer-hymns...
...with clarinets and percussion,
there will be created...
...an incredible sound.
We will make a contract for five years.
Three years are gratis and we will
take over all extras.
That will become a new trend.
What means "Trend"?
"Trend" is the name of the mosque
that is built in Taksim.
- I didn't hear anything about it.
- Neither did I. Come uncle!
Come you!
The angels are descending
gullibly from heaven!
Making a chants tape for so cheap?
God will curse us.
Sibel, there has been a woman here.
I believe, she wants to invest in our
company.
Will we wait a little until we
will drive home? Butler!
The wedding will be delayed.
It doesn't matter. We can wait...
We have to decide right now.
I am pregnant.
# I woke up without you this morning
# It doesn't work without you
# Even my first cigarette did not taste well
# Love is zero-balance
# It doesn't work without you
# A love, that got balance
# I had to ask me again
- # Why do I want you so much?
- I love you.
# Come, my angel, let me love your nice
face also
Silence!
What did he do evil to this poor girl!
Look at her, how miserable!
Son of a bitch!
I call you in order to wish you good
recovery.
If that swine touches you again,
I will kill him!
His own mother will not recognise him.
Hello?
Thank you very much.
Look, the beauty of our shop is
coming again, Hayri.
How beautiful. Like a jewel, like flowers!
- Hello!
- Hello brother.
Where is the fairy queen?
Friends, for the hail of our land, our nation
we even owe money to the painters.
That all happens, because money is
coming in. We have to find her.
Hello. Miss Firuze!
Here is Orhan.
We just have spoken of you.
All ready. The shop, we also are shining.
Please, one minute.
I will fetch Ferhat. For you!
Where? Grand Cevahir, what time?
Of course. The song..,
Thank you very much.
We will see each other.
- Did she make available money?
- That she didn't say.
She only told something about heritage
complications.
Oh no! Delay until tomorrow
would be deadly.
No, we have to maintain. Main point
the box will be edited.
Oh no, we can't enter the hotel in these
clothes.
Let us buy some clothes at Vakko.
Wait, not too fast. That is not suitable to us!
We don't want to blame our name.
The Turkish people are living for
honour and fame.
We will find something suitable.
By your love I have come into this
miserable situation.
I possessed everything except you.
# By your love I have come into this
miserable situation
# I possessed everything except you
# I didn't fear rain and have gone my way
# I get goose-flesh by thinking, that you
maybe are not at home
# If we would make love, we would
drink until daylight
# I wouldn't go to my work and you
wouldn't go home
# I get goose-flesh:
what to do, if you will not be at home
Impossible, children!
I am always at home.
Let us come to the box.
We need good advertising.
Posters in all streets. The newspaper
get a whole page with advertising.
We could shoot a clip also, couldn't we?
Why not black-white?
The pink at the suit is the first thing, that
gets a colour.
Because of the name "Flower-fields".
Children, make a budget for the open air
concertin the stadium.
Everything at summer. The concerts in
Aspendos are the most important events.
- That is true.
- An excellent idea.
Hopefully you don't think: "We have found
a rich chicken in order to pluck.
Oh no, how can you think this of us!
I have a good feeling for investments.
You have inspired me to the
enchanting formula,
that opens the gate of my country.
I have sought for it several years.
Never could I find the entrance.
What do you say?
You are looking upon a splendid future,
but you have to believe on it. Like I do.
- Right!
Friends, do you feel arising synergy,
when we are together?
Now close your eyes and take the
hands of your neighbours.
Do you feel the force?
I do in fact.
You see: that is it!
Yes, I feel different.
- That's it!
- Yes, it has happened.
This is always.
I believe, you have found a gold-mine
again, miss Firuze.
Now the work is following.
This gentleman is the owner.
- He is serving me personally, every time I
come- He is honour and pleasure to me.
- Hello.
- Mr Ferhat,
there are important things we have to
talk about. Afterwards?
Hello. I am a fan of yours, Angel.
You inspired me the charmed words to
open the gate to my real country
that I searched for years and couldn't
find the entrance to.
I discovered this code with you. If I
lose you, I'll forget it again.
I dreamt that you were a sweet little girl
a soft, mellow lover, a warm friend.
I am standing right besides you.
A man can only stand behind you.
Shadowed by you,
under your wide wings.
An invisible hand keeps me away.
The man you desire does not know
how this feels like.
May I be that man?
- Kürþat give me that!
- You are hiding a thing.
I am not hiding anything!
Give me that please!
What did you do?
Maybe all I wanted was
to sing a song together.
An ordinary, cute song.
I wish you could hear it.
Where is Kürþat?
To hit a woman?
No! I didn't do anything.
I will beat the living daylights out of you!
Where is the prick of that dog?
Sell and give out the money!
Damned what will happen to us, you
bastard?
I swear you, I will take revenge.
My father is keeping me short.
He doesn't give me money any more.
We will cut you
into little slices.
Your eyes you son of a bitch,
superb ass-hole!
You will always remember this view.
You have to pay the saxophone-player
and our share on what has been sold
right now-!
I am here in order to protect you.
In order to save your life,
respecting your father.
You are here in Turkey.
If you park your car you have to pay
in order to prevent damages to your car.
Tayyar has to give you some money.
We marry you off!
Than it will be okay, otherwise!
You get addicted in this way!
A practical joke! You are to much fan of the
Americans!
Help me!
- Have you seen it?
- What than?
- Were not you there?
- No, I haven't seen anything.
Please select for me, I have to call that girl!
Hello sweetheart, It's me.
Are you at home? I will come
and call for you.
A concert in Aspendos.
I have enough of the popular press.
There is no more privacy! I want to alter just
this,do you understand?
I want to share my life and these endless
disruptions only with you.
I love you!
Melek, marry me!
Why do we stop?
I believe, that's your house.
- One moment, Ibrahim, what's the matter?
- Hayri, Hayri!
- That's our justice.
- Take it easy, time is over.
Do you understand?
The weather is beautiful, the field free.
The better one should win!
Nevertheless you have to suffer a little bit!
- For gods sake!
- Come, fair play, fair play!
- We have a partner, a sponsor, control it!
- Money is no problem.
Your investor is this harmless Ferhat?
- Are you responsible for the money?
- Please?
- Six millions please.
- What do you mean?
Money for two three-million-bullets.
- We haven't that much!
- Give him all, what we have!
- We have three million.
- Make your heels free.
- Please wait still! Oh god!
- Let me speak please!
Hello!
This is our partner and sponsor,
our soul and everything.
How are you?
These bandits assert, that you are their
partner. I don't believe them, but...
- It is true. - We have a little problem, that
we probably will solve with you.
Which bank?
The cash-pay-record-shop,
if you want an other bank...
- Your money will be there tomorrow.
How much? - 88000 in $!
That's too much, what do you think,
mister Orhan?
I am your opinion, but mister Ýbrahim has a
different vision.
- One half cash, the other one in rates.
- That's convenient!
Tomorrow, but you will be dead,
if there is any delay, for what reason ever!
Please, that doesn't go!
- At ten o'clock.
- Ten!
Please close the door behind you.
- We will see tomorrow.
- If you permit.
- Come now!
- There is nothing wrong?
Are you joking?
Please give me my three millions.
Thank you!
Orhan, take it please! Okay,
now we will go also.
- Let us tidy up the papers.
- Okay, later, so I say bye-bye.
- Ferhat? Are you well?
- Yes and you?
Riddle please, why I have come.
- I believe to know it.
- Who is that?
- A poster, only for decoration.
- Did you expect me?
Yes, I did.
Is this your bed?
- Yes, if you sit down...
- Am I allowed to sit down?
Of course.
Come,
I have to say you something but how?
Sometimes there are feelings for
somebody at once...
...you know, for somebody, who is totally
foreign. It simply comes.
Yes, I understand.
Properly one should say it open-minded,
but it is...
difficult to find the right words.
- I agree with you.
You...
You are a beautiful man.
- No, that is only your...
- Wonderful! Great!
- You are great also.
- You are like a star.
- Your behaviour should be star-like also!
- All right.
- Do trust yourself.
- All right, all right.
You don't think, that I am trying to take profit
of this situation, do you?
It is good to be open-minded.
Properly I know very well, what you are
suffering.
Let us not play together. I am so confused to
make it short:
it has no sense.
Ferhat,
I know you have fallen in love with me
totally!
# Fifty stars are shining in heaven.
You can see them clearly
# Eyes are treating furtive love
# You can read unspoken love in the eyes
# A loving bird doesn't know food and water
# Could I come together with my
beloved one time a year?
There is ever no trace of your partner.
What's your
comment upon it?
What do you tell me there?
I have said, I can't take profit of the
situation. That's what she has said.
What does it mean? Couldn't he say:
come and take profit of me'?
No, Tayyar, his boy has received two slaps.
He is crying right at the moment.
- Dear Ibrahim.
- What do you say? What?
That lady has opened an account.
Of course she has paid on this account.
What else?
- Push play, you bastard!
- Dear Ýbrahim!
Let us fix the money. Thereafter we will
speak with Tayyar.
We will have an orgy of circumcision or
something like it. Doubtless you will make it.
Okay, you still have one hour.
If it goes wrong, you know what is
waiting for you!
We will be there soon with the
money-bundles. In which way we will bear them?
It's the wrong time for jokes!
I would like to withdraw money.
Of course, but there is no account
on your name.
Really? Can I speak with the
directress please?
We have a director.
Is this the wrong address?
Miss Firuze? We don't have this client.
I can't remember, we have had her
in former days.
# You are like black ribbon, Firuze
# In your eyes there is haste
# The years are too slow for you
# Why are you in hurry? Wait
If your wheel don't have gaps, you are
a newcomer in this profession.
Tayyar!
How did you discover it?
We will take Tayyar Baba into our club.
Come, my dear, come!
I ask you for advice.
Do you permit?
- Do come into the basin!
- I come.
Are you able to swim?
Are you joking? I have grown up at the
beach of the Black Sea.
We are like this fish.
We have come in order to attack.
- Where are the life-belts?
- We have no more of them!
Now. Come to me!
- Orhan, Who was this?
- Whom do you mean?
- That one, who just past before?
- Tayyar's son.
- What do you say?
- Daddy, the invitations will come today.
- You could drown.
- I have a boy with a terrific voice.
Could you give us an extra.
For example an...
...a party of circumcision or something
like it. -I'll pay the singers.
I found this boy from Germany. You have
token him.
Your Melih took my singer, seduced her and
fathered a child with her. Fuck!
Hayri! I come!
- He is drowning!
- Good heaven!
Orhan, look at him!
Everybody is praising your voice.
Let hear it!
- I have saved you, Hayri!
- So sing!
Sing nightingale, sing!
# Your heaven were blue, so blue
# The clouds were silver, your hair was
white
# There is a rain, so sad and gloomy
# When you laugh, tears should flow upon
my hands
# A woman, white, quiet and enchanting
# A woman, wet, fine and warm
# She has to be sorceress of the songs
- Will you marry? - He asked my hand right
at the moment, I wanted to leave him.
He says, that he loves me.
Forget this person finally!
Advertising, a role in a movie...
You could earn a lot of money.
The Turkish cinema has future.
Acting is worse than living with Kürþat!
I hardly can wear the hungry eyes of the
spectators.
I cannot endure fashion-shows,
the stage, the camera's!
All are looking at me unbrokenly, no!
Who is there?
I know: the person, who has
written the letter.
I haven't read the rest, but it was very fine.
Are you still there?
Please speak!
Properly I would like to get to know you.
What did he say?
How does he know it?
Except Melih the whole world
will know it already.
Sweetheart, if we could regulate your
blood-pressure in some way!
I never sang pop before, but you know,
I am apt to do it.
Could you talk about it once more?
Where is the serum?
Hayri will get work of Tayyar, isn't it?
We will get money.
The medicine is sure.
Even with the medicine it will be very
difficult, Seyfi.
Don't you know it? Don't you know the
serious condition of the patient?
- You want the baby unconditionally?
- There is nothing, what I could do.
Go out, friends! Don't stress the girl without
necessity.
Next week we will shoot Ferhat's clip.
Who is the director?
- You!
- My love,
if you would be a little healthier, you
could come to the set with me.
Everything is black and
white until an angel arrives, who brings
a baby with wings.
When the baby comes, the clip will
get colours.
It is dedicated to you.
Sezen Aksu is seeking a soprano.
# Let me pass
# My pot has been filled by gifts
# I know neither sins nor damage
# I am burning of pain
# So I have got the pain
# What a strange way
# Sometimes I lost him, other times
I found him again
# I wobbled and didn't move
any more. Let me pass
# Give me my head
# I can't sacrifice myself
# I can't loose myself, can't separate
me of myself
It is the second time, that a haven't got
shampoo in my eyes.
- It will not work.
- I already said, I don't leave my artists.
I have been angry with you,
but next time I will bring you out.
Don't worry about it!
Main point we got the party.
The rest will be easy!
The only thing is, that...
We have to organise the fare still.
That is easy.
But Ferhat needs a stage-costume.
# Renew my fate, Kahtalým. Do create me
one time more
You king of all barbers. Good morning.
How are you?
Also, I am very happy,
I started a new diet and work on a new box.
The whole country will speak about it.
Now I am coming out! I am coming!
Come here. Didn't you have a suit for us,
did you? Come!
- Please, stand besides him!
- Why?
It will be a little too wide, but it is
the same size.
Don't mind. Wide will be in the
fashion this year.
Heaven, don't talk such humbug!
- Besides: to where do you want to go?
- To my village.
No, never. You have a contract!
But Hayri Abi didn't want me
at all. Neither did miss Sansar.
Accordingly I am displaced here.
I have your rights on the box. Look
what has been written!
It is valid in the whole galaxy
do you understand, sweety?
Fucked nightingale!
But where is the music?
We have fixed everything except the music!
Music is everywhere, man!
In the bus, in the streets, in the heads
of the people,
in shops, restaurants, at brokers,
everywhere!
Music is eaten and drunk during
footballgames and elections.
One is cursing with music and in this
country no love is swore without music!
- Please drive to the right side. I want
to bale out. - To where?
I have forgotten something in the
hotel. I will return immediately.
Don't come too late, otherwise I will
loose my temper!
All right, I will be there!
- Come soon, okay?
- You engage young talents?
For the concert tonight.
Am I allowed to recite, please?
- He has to, Hayri?
- Do sing, I have said already!
# Does love forgive everything thanks
former happy days?
# Does time make forget?
- Do you know miss Firuze?
- Yes. She is living in this palace.
- She was seeking a room for a girlfriend.
- Where,which palace?
- Miss Firuze! I did seek you everywhere...
- Excuse me!
I beg you pardon, I mixed up you with
miss Firuze.
So the broker and your dress...
Please, let us go in.
Excuse me please. I just came from Cyprus.
- How do you know miss Firuze?
- She is our producer.
What does she produce?
We make music and give concerts.
So she has changed her profession?
Whom do I see there? Welcome.
Welcome.
Please, miss Firuze, take it easy!
Could I speak with you outside?
I don't understand, why my clothes?
She was healing already.
But than the illness took another way.
- I did not registry it. It went too fast.
- We have to drive away this group!
Sorry, but what is the matter with her?
Miss Firuze has seen you at T.V.
She has thought, you had been fallen in
love with her.
The brain is an enigma.
- What does she have?
- Schizophrenia.
What does this mean, schizophrenia?
If you are speaking with god, they call it
prayer.
If god is speaking to you,
they call it schizophrenia.
If my colleges could hear this!
- And the other people? -They are my other
patients therapy for groups!
So she doesn't have money?
Sir, Firuze has been born in this palace.
She has grown up here.
But how do I have to say?
Their parents were assisting miss Süreyya's.
- So this place?
- This is her house.
She has established the company of
schizophrenia.
- I understand.
- Hello, we telephoned.
It has been paid money on your off shore
account.
Mister Ferhat, it is a honour for us, to
receive artists like you in our bank.
I have to bring Firuze back to her father.
- Mister Ferhat!- If you permit, I would like
to speak with the gentleman.
He has to be confronted with reality!
Where is he?
What did he say to him?
- The truth.
- He has gone thereafter?
What is reality?
You have disappointed him.
That was not our aim.
What does rest after saying the truth?
If you are real, I am a lie.
A paradise without angels!
# The curse of the devil is in the songs
# filled by enthousiasm my
situation is serious
# This game is always bad. My dices
always are marked
# It is the endless game, that is
played by fate
# If the dices fall in this way
# I use to love the beautiful but they
have to be young
# The heart is incorrigible
Look at Hoca and Tatu!
They are having fun.
Let them enjoy themselves.
Why did you come here?
What did you do?
The ambience is very good. Will I let
dance Halay?
No, wait! Delay what you can.
Go on until they become red.
Ferhat, wo do you stay?
- All are waiting for you!
- I am no more of the game.
- What does this mean?
- I am not of the game.
- Come and rise!
- No, let me. Why are you here?
Because of this money. If I could
get some of it...
I will buy a ticket to my country.
This guy really does want to become slim.
Look at this! All personalities
of the world of records and newspapers
have come.
- But where is this little bastard?
- Take it easy and sit down.
This person always has depressions.
What for?
As if his beloved has been fucked.
This damned, stupid german!
- Go, Ferhat.
- Give up me, Melih!
Why do you give up this dream?
It is because a girl, isn't it?
- Why not?
- I also am in love.
Therefor I can't sing there now.
- Who is she, man?
- Melek.
Melek?
It is her wedding.
- How are you? -You are honouring us.
Thank you very much!
Tayyar will kill us. Who is acting
in stead of Ferhat?
No. Studio yes. I am no type for stage.
Will we get off with the money?
In taht case we are lost...
Who was it?
Go well.
There are no problems, are there?
- No problems. Everything goes digitally!
- Flowers!
- Look, what I have for you.
- What's that?
My bill. Tayyar gave me the advance.
You have to pay the musicians with the rest.
You beggars.
Tayyar will present you an account also.
I didn't want to say it, but the musicians get
their money from another source.
- That's not true!
- It is. I got the rest in cheque.
- Tayyar does understand you.
- Where is the artist?
Without money no artist.
You have to know it.
The son of the "heel-killer" wants to marry
and you leave the wedding-party.
Gratulations, you have courage.
- Do you pay at least value added tax?
- Don't worry, we will fix it.
They shoot, if we stay.
But also, if we try to flee.
We have a umbrella inside.
And they have opened it.
The movie has ended. But they don't write
"end".
You have to see it.
- What is the matter?
- What kind of movie?
Ýbrahim und Sansar put the money
in their pocket
and didn't pay the orchestra. We are lost.
It is all right! An entry at this wedding
wouldn't be suitable to you!
It would not be suitable to you also.
Fortunately we have no entry!
- Do you know, why we are loosing?
- Why?
Why we are capitulating always?
Because we always, we always...
- How?
- Why?
- We are to honest!
- Humbug!
Really.
It is true.
It is softening you up finally.
- I have been softened up.
- Yes, it softens you up.
You have to take it easy sometimes.
Cheers? I would kill the person,
who has served me this serum, in the
middle of Taksim-square.
Stop it, Seyfi.
He makes me furious!
Melih,
we should let it be.
You are wright.
If we are already on our way...
- If we suicide...
- We do it living.
# Forgive me
# It is too early for loosing and too late for
loving
# Forgive me
Sir Tayyar
Forbidden, I let if forbid in Turkeye and now
he is acting on my party!
# At least your name should remain at the
end of broken things
# Pursued by Lonelyness
# Forgive me
# At time of my love
# There still has been rain in this city
Kill the bastard!
# Forgive me
# It is too early for loosing
# And too late for loving
# Forgive me
# At time of my love
# There still has been rain in this city
# Love was as heavy as led in this city
# Forgive me
# The poems of your eyes
# The songs of your hair
Did you really want to kill me or not?
Death is the end of all suffering.
We are on earth in order
to make suffering so that hell can be
unburdened.
- Wag, you are really sensitive!
- Yes very.
That is a part of my profession.
Sometimes feelings are stronger than
reason.
Let us make a box for you.
That was only a joke!
Here a demo. Listen to it!
- I will apply to you.
- Of course you will.
- Certainly I will apply.
- So do it!
- I did say it, haven't I?
- Yes, you will excuse me now.
- What's the matter?
- We will throw out you immediately.
That's how the profession is like.
We will break one or two of your
bones also. By tradition.
Do you prefer some of them?
Properly we prefer an existing bone
Orhan, flee!
What do you look? Get them!
# There is no return. I have put fire
to all my ships
# This masked ball with all these false
# faces is unbearable to me
One mosque is not enough to you, uncle?
Let us go.
Let us save them.
You believe, it is a fire?
Is the basis ready?
All ready, in remembrance to our
common nights.
Wait! Firuze, where are you?
Ferhat has found Firuze.
Don't believe, that it is the end.
The endless competition never will stop.
They will weep a lot about us and they will
laugh.
Now all together.
# Starving melodies are snaring my heart
# Such a dream, as there were merely songs
# Flying birds seagulls
# A sweet and green springtime
# Laughing and merry love-pairs
# Here were sorrows, there desires
# Such a sea of loving waves
I have token everything from hospital.
I don't want to come with you now.
Everybody should decide for himself.
No, impossible.
We have begun together
and we will end together.
It is better, that he doesn't know, that he
has a poor father.
It doesn't mind, that I will not be there.
I am a burden.
He should throw me off.
It is the end for me but I am sorry, that
I have put you with me.
That's not necessary! Cheers!
Now the end has come finally.
Sorry, I haven't succeeded.
Sorry, I have a gastric ulcer.
They have gone!
- Seyfi?
- Melih!
Ferhat?
- Ferhat, wake up, my boy.
- I beg you!
We are loosing him! Run, keep water.
Please, come!
Ferhat, wake up.
- You coward!
- Where is Firuze?
We have been reborn.
Friends, let us start at zero again.
Nobody can halt us.
We will found a new company with
a colourful name.
The turn is on us, to serve electric shocks
like the fish under the sand.
What was his name?
RA- RAY!
To Hilmi Topaloglu.
Scandal at the wedding!
Their album has been sold 2 million copies.
Turkey is talking about them.
"I was a lighter, I became a director. Now it's
Hollywood!"
We all owe it to Firuze.
Melek broke up with her lover.
Firuze still at large.