Yes, I was very popular.
Well, it was a pleasure to me, mister Ferhat.
- So to us, at any case.
- Ferhat will accompany you until your car!
Of course.
Don't forget: The beginning is the half
business.
The end is the other half.
If you want to kill yourself, do it by living.
- And where do you live?
- In an hotel, in cartoon.
Hotel Cartoon? Understand.
Hotels
ever give a bad feeling.
The sorrows and pains of the guests use
to remain in the rooms.
- Rent a house.
- Okay.
On the backside of the mosque you will find
"Home Immoveables".
Remember me to mister Sadettin. He will
take sorrow for the house.
- Thank you very much, why do you do that?
- What?
Why do you help us?
You has called me and I have come.
You will get a cold in this weather.
- That's not important. -I have sent
away my driver. I will take a taxi.
I will call for a taxi.
Please wait. I will tell you something.
I didn't drive by bus since school-time.
You would take a city-bus?
Do you see, that you too have influence.
I have been changed by you.
Nevertheless you should not claim
this too much.
Please what?
The human being doesn't register
his own life.
He has to learn, how to live. See you soon.
Hello.
What are you doing. Bring the things
downstairs!
We have counted the days also.
We will pay you cash...
I don't want it!
This debt-story has no end.
We will edit your box also.
- Which box?
- That one with the prayers.
The angels came down from heaven, so
pure.
- No prayer for the soul. Hymns with
prayers!- That is also beautiful.
I get goose-flesh, Hayri.
Cut off! You are producing boxes
for bitches in order to...
...mix them with my prayer-hymns.
I don't want a box!
We of Umut Music will renew the
structures of our company.
If we bring out your prayer-hymns...
...with clarinets and percussion,
there will be created...
...an incredible sound.
We will make a contract for five years.
Three years are gratis and we will
take over all extras.
That will become a new trend.
What means "Trend"?
"Trend" is the name of the mosque
that is built in Taksim.
- I didn't hear anything about it.
- Neither did I. Come uncle!
Come you!
The angels are descending
gullibly from heaven!
Making a chants tape for so cheap?
God will curse us.
Sibel, there has been a woman here.
I believe, she wants to invest in our
company.
Will we wait a little until we
will drive home? Butler!
The wedding will be delayed.
It doesn't matter. We can wait...
We have to decide right now.
I am pregnant.
# I woke up without you this morning
# It doesn't work without you
# Even my first cigarette did not taste well
# Love is zero-balance
# It doesn't work without you
# A love, that got balance
# I had to ask me again
- # Why do I want you so much?
- I love you.
# Come, my angel, let me love your nice
face also
Silence!
What did he do evil to this poor girl!
Look at her, how miserable!
Son of a bitch!
I call you in order to wish you good
recovery.
If that swine touches you again,
I will kill him!
His own mother will not recognise him.
Hello?
Thank you very much.
Look, the beauty of our shop is
coming again, Hayri.
How beautiful. Like a jewel, like flowers!
- Hello!
- Hello brother.
Where is the fairy queen?
Friends, for the hail of our land, our nation
we even owe money to the painters.
That all happens, because money is
coming in. We have to find her.
Hello. Miss Firuze!
Here is Orhan.
We just have spoken of you.
All ready. The shop, we also are shining.
Please, one minute.
I will fetch Ferhat. For you!
Where? Grand Cevahir, what time?
Of course. The song..,
Thank you very much.
We will see each other.
- Did she make available money?
- That she didn't say.
She only told something about heritage
complications.
Oh no! Delay until tomorrow
would be deadly.
No, we have to maintain. Main point
the box will be edited.
Oh no, we can't enter the hotel in these
clothes.
Let us buy some clothes at Vakko.
Wait, not too fast. That is not suitable to us!
We don't want to blame our name.
The Turkish people are living for
honour and fame.
We will find something suitable.
By your love I have come into this
miserable situation.
I possessed everything except you.
# By your love I have come into this
miserable situation
# I possessed everything except you
# I didn't fear rain and have gone my way
# I get goose-flesh by thinking, that you
maybe are not at home
# If we would make love, we would
drink until daylight
# I wouldn't go to my work and you
wouldn't go home
# I get goose-flesh:
what to do, if you will not be at home
Impossible, children!
I am always at home.
Let us come to the box.
We need good advertising.
Posters in all streets. The newspaper
get a whole page with advertising.
We could shoot a clip also, couldn't we?
Why not black-white?
The pink at the suit is the first thing, that
gets a colour.
Because of the name "Flower-fields".
Children, make a budget for the open air
concertin the stadium.
Everything at summer. The concerts in
Aspendos are the most important events.
- That is true.
- An excellent idea.
Hopefully you don't think: "We have found
a rich chicken in order to pluck.
Oh no, how can you think this of us!
I have a good feeling for investments.
You have inspired me to the
enchanting formula,
that opens the gate of my country.
I have sought for it several years.
Never could I find the entrance.
What do you say?
You are looking upon a splendid future,
but you have to believe on it. Like I do.
- Right!
Friends, do you feel arising synergy,
when we are together?
Now close your eyes and take the
hands of your neighbours.
Do you feel the force?
I do in fact.
You see: that is it!
Yes, I feel different.
- That's it!
- Yes, it has happened.
This is always.
I believe, you have found a gold-mine
again, miss Firuze.
Now the work is following.
This gentleman is the owner.
- He is serving me personally, every time I
come- He is honour and pleasure to me.
- Hello.
- Mr Ferhat,
there are important things we have to
talk about. Afterwards?
Hello. I am a fan of yours, Angel.
You inspired me the charmed words to
open the gate to my real country
that I searched for years and couldn't
find the entrance to.
I discovered this code with you. If I
lose you, I'll forget it again.
I dreamt that you were a sweet little girl
a soft, mellow lover, a warm friend.
I am standing right besides you.
A man can only stand behind you.
Shadowed by you,
under your wide wings.
An invisible hand keeps me away.
The man you desire does not know
how this feels like.
May I be that man?
- Kürþat give me that!
- You are hiding a thing.
I am not hiding anything!
Give me that please!
What did you do?
Maybe all I wanted was
to sing a song together.
An ordinary, cute song.
I wish you could hear it.
Where is Kürþat?
To hit a woman?
No! I didn't do anything.
I will beat the living daylights out of you!
Where is the prick of that dog?
Sell and give out the money!
Damned what will happen to us, you
bastard?
I swear you, I will take revenge.
My father is keeping me short.
He doesn't give me money any more.
We will cut you
into little slices.
Your eyes you son of a bitch,
superb ass-hole!
You will always remember this view.
You have to pay the saxophone-player
and our share on what has been sold
right now-!
I am here in order to protect you.
In order to save your life,
respecting your father.
You are here in Turkey.
If you park your car you have to pay
in order to prevent damages to your car.
Tayyar has to give you some money.
We marry you off!
Than it will be okay, otherwise!
You get addicted in this way!
A practical joke! You are to much fan of the
Americans!
Help me!
- Have you seen it?
- What than?
- Were not you there?
- No, I haven't seen anything.
Please select for me, I have to call that girl!
Hello sweetheart, It's me.
Are you at home? I will come
and call for you.
A concert in Aspendos.
I have enough of the popular press.
There is no more privacy! I want to alter just
this,do you understand?
I want to share my life and these endless
disruptions only with you.
I love you!
Melek, marry me!
Why do we stop?
I believe, that's your house.
- One moment, Ibrahim, what's the matter?
- Hayri, Hayri!
- That's our justice.
- Take it easy, time is over.
Do you understand?
The weather is beautiful, the field free.
The better one should win!
Nevertheless you have to suffer a little bit!
- For gods sake!
- Come, fair play, fair play!
- We have a partner, a sponsor, control it!
- Money is no problem.
Your investor is this harmless Ferhat?
- Are you responsible for the money?
- Please?
- Six millions please.
- What do you mean?
Money for two three-million-bullets.
- We haven't that much!
- Give him all, what we have!
- We have three million.
- Make your heels free.
- Please wait still! Oh god!
- Let me speak please!
Hello!
This is our partner and sponsor,
our soul and everything.
How are you?
These bandits assert, that you are their
partner. I don't believe them, but...
- It is true. - We have a little problem, that
we probably will solve with you.
Which bank?
The cash-pay-record-shop,
if you want an other bank...
- Your money will be there tomorrow.
How much? - 88000 in $!
That's too much, what do you think,
mister Orhan?
I am your opinion, but mister Ýbrahim has a
different vision.
- One half cash, the other one in rates.
- That's convenient!
Tomorrow, but you will be dead,
if there is any delay, for what reason ever!
Please, that doesn't go!
- At ten o'clock.
- Ten!
Please close the door behind you.
- We will see tomorrow.
- If you permit.
- Come now!
- There is nothing wrong?
Are you joking?
Please give me my three millions.
Thank you!
Orhan, take it please! Okay,
now we will go also.
- Let us tidy up the papers.
- Okay, later, so I say bye-bye.
- Ferhat? Are you well?
- Yes and you?
Riddle please, why I have come.
- I believe to know it.
- Who is that?
- A poster, only for decoration.
- Did you expect me?
Yes, I did.
Is this your bed?
- Yes, if you sit down...
- Am I allowed to sit down?
Of course.
Come,
I have to say you something but how?
Sometimes there are feelings for
somebody at once...
...you know, for somebody, who is totally
foreign. It simply comes.
Yes, I understand.
Properly one should say it open-minded,
but it is...
difficult to find the right words.
- I agree with you.
You...
You are a beautiful man.
- No, that is only your...
- Wonderful! Great!
- You are great also.
- You are like a star.
- Your behaviour should be star-like also!
- All right.
- Do trust yourself.
- All right, all right.
You don't think, that I am trying to take profit
of this situation, do you?
It is good to be open-minded.
Properly I know very well, what you are
suffering.
Let us not play together. I am so confused to
make it short:
it has no sense.
Ferhat,
I know you have fallen in love with me
totally!
# Fifty stars are shining in heaven.
You can see them clearly
# Eyes are treating furtive love
# You can read unspoken love in the eyes
# A loving bird doesn't know food and water
# Could I come together with my
beloved one time a year?
There is ever no trace of your partner.
What's your
comment upon it?
What do you tell me there?
I have said, I can't take profit of the
situation. That's what she has said.
What does it mean? Couldn't he say:
come and take profit of me'?
No, Tayyar, his boy has received two slaps.
He is crying right at the moment.
- Dear Ibrahim.
- What do you say? What?
That lady has opened an account.
Of course she has paid on this account.
What else?
- Push play, you bastard!
- Dear Ýbrahim!
Let us fix the money. Thereafter we will
speak with Tayyar.
We will have an orgy of circumcision or
something like it. Doubtless you will make it.
Okay, you still have one hour.
If it goes wrong, you know what is
waiting for you!
We will be there soon with the
money-bundles. In which way we will bear them?
It's the wrong time for jokes!
I would like to withdraw money.
Of course, but there is no account
on your name.
Really? Can I speak with the
directress please?
We have a director.
Is this the wrong address?
Miss Firuze? We don't have this client.
I can't remember, we have had her
in former days.
# You are like black ribbon, Firuze
# In your eyes there is haste
# The years are too slow for you
# Why are you in hurry? Wait
If your wheel don't have gaps, you are
a newcomer in this profession.
Tayyar!
How did you discover it?
We will take Tayyar Baba into our club.
Come, my dear, come!
I ask you for advice.
Do you permit?
- Do come into the basin!
- I come.
Are you able to swim?
Are you joking? I have grown up at the
beach of the Black Sea.
We are like this fish.
We have come in order to attack.
- Where are the life-belts?
- We have no more of them!
Now. Come to me!
- Orhan, Who was this?
- Whom do you mean?
- That one, who just past before?
- Tayyar's son.
- What do you say?
- Daddy, the invitations will come today.
- You could drown.
- I have a boy with a terrific voice.
Could you give us an extra.
For example an...
...a party of circumcision or something
like it. -I'll pay the singers.
I found this boy from Germany. You have
token him.
Your Melih took my singer, seduced her and
fathered a child with her. Fuck!
Hayri! I come!
- He is drowning!
- Good heaven!
Orhan, look at him!
Everybody is praising your voice.
Let hear it!
- I have saved you, Hayri!
- So sing!
Sing nightingale, sing!
# Your heaven were blue, so blue
# The clouds were silver, your hair was
white
# There is a rain, so sad and gloomy
# When you laugh, tears should flow upon
my hands
# A woman, white, quiet and enchanting
# A woman, wet, fine and warm
# She has to be sorceress of the songs
- Will you marry? - He asked my hand right
at the moment, I wanted to leave him.
He says, that he loves me.
Forget this person finally!
Advertising, a role in a movie...
You could earn a lot of money.
The Turkish cinema has future.
Acting is worse than living with Kürþat!
I hardly can wear the hungry eyes of the
spectators.
I cannot endure fashion-shows,
the stage, the camera's!
All are looking at me unbrokenly, no!
Who is there?
I know: the person, who has
written the letter.
I haven't read the rest, but it was very fine.
Are you still there?
Please speak!
Properly I would like to get to know you.
What did he say?
How does he know it?
Except Melih the whole world
will know it already.
Sweetheart, if we could regulate your
blood-pressure in some way!
I never sang pop before, but you know,
I am apt to do it.
Could you talk about it once more?
Where is the serum?
Hayri will get work of Tayyar, isn't it?
We will get money.
The medicine is sure.
Even with the medicine it will be very
difficult, Seyfi.
Don't you know it? Don't you know the
serious condition of the patient?
- You want the baby unconditionally?
- There is nothing, what I could do.
Go out, friends! Don't stress the girl without
necessity.
Next week we will shoot Ferhat's clip.
Who is the director?
- You!
- My love,
if you would be a little healthier, you
could come to the set with me.
Everything is black and
white until an angel arrives, who brings
a baby with wings.
When the baby comes, the clip will
get colours.
It is dedicated to you.
Sezen Aksu is seeking a soprano.
# Let me pass
# My pot has been filled by gifts
# I know neither sins nor damage
# I am burning of pain
# So I have got the pain
# What a strange way
# Sometimes I lost him, other times
I found him again
# I wobbled and didn't move
any more. Let me pass
# Give me my head
# I can't sacrifice myself
# I can't loose myself, can't separate
me of myself
It is the second time, that a haven't got
shampoo in my eyes.
- It will not work.
- I already said, I don't leave my artists.
I have been angry with you,
but next time I will bring you out.
Don't worry about it!
Main point we got the party.
The rest will be easy!
The only thing is, that...
We have to organise the fare still.
That is easy.
But Ferhat needs a stage-costume.
# Renew my fate, Kahtalým. Do create me
one time more
You king of all barbers. Good morning.
How are you?
Also, I am very happy,
I started a new diet and work on a new box.
The whole country will speak about it.
Now I am coming out! I am coming!
Come here. Didn't you have a suit for us,
did you? Come!
- Please, stand besides him!
- Why?
It will be a little too wide, but it is
the same size.
Don't mind. Wide will be in the
fashion this year.
Heaven, don't talk such humbug!
- Besides: to where do you want to go?
- To my village.
No, never. You have a contract!
But Hayri Abi didn't want me
at all. Neither did miss Sansar.
Accordingly I am displaced here.
I have your rights on the box. Look
what has been written!
It is valid in the whole galaxy
do you understand, sweety?
Fucked nightingale!
But where is the music?
We have fixed everything except the music!
Music is everywhere, man!
In the bus, in the streets, in the heads
of the people,
in shops, restaurants, at brokers,
everywhere!
Music is eaten and drunk during
footballgames and elections.
One is cursing with music and in this
country no love is swore without music!
- Please drive to the right side. I want
to bale out. - To where?
I have forgotten something in the
hotel. I will return immediately.
Don't come too late, otherwise I will
loose my temper!
All right, I will be there!
- Come soon, okay?
- You engage young talents?
For the concert tonight.
Am I allowed to recite, please?
- He has to, Hayri?
- Do sing, I have said already!
# Does love forgive everything thanks
former happy days?
# Does time make forget?
- Do you know miss Firuze?
- Yes. She is living in this palace.
- She was seeking a room for a girlfriend.
- Where,which palace?
- Miss Firuze! I did seek you everywhere...
- Excuse me!
I beg you pardon, I mixed up you with
miss Firuze.
So the broker and your dress...
Please, let us go in.
Excuse me please. I just came from Cyprus.
- How do you know miss Firuze?
- She is our producer.
What does she produce?
We make music and give concerts.
So she has changed her profession?
Whom do I see there? Welcome.
Welcome.
Please, miss Firuze, take it easy!
Could I speak with you outside?
I don't understand, why my clothes?
She was healing already.
But than the illness took another way.
- I did not registry it. It went too fast.
- We have to drive away this group!
Sorry, but what is the matter with her?
Miss Firuze has seen you at T.V.
She has thought, you had been fallen in
love with her.
The brain is an enigma.
- What does she have?
- Schizophrenia.
What does this mean, schizophrenia?
If you are speaking with god, they call it
prayer.
If god is speaking to you,
they call it schizophrenia.
If my colleges could hear this!
- And the other people? -They are my other
patients therapy for groups!
So she doesn't have money?
Sir, Firuze has been born in this palace.
She has grown up here.
But how do I have to say?
Their parents were assisting miss Süreyya's.
- So this place?
- This is her house.
She has established the company of
schizophrenia.
- I understand.
- Hello, we telephoned.
It has been paid money on your off shore
account.
Mister Ferhat, it is a honour for us, to
receive artists like you in our bank.
I have to bring Firuze back to her father.
- Mister Ferhat!- If you permit, I would like
to speak with the gentleman.
He has to be confronted with reality!
Where is he?
What did he say to him?
- The truth.
- He has gone thereafter?
What is reality?
You have disappointed him.
That was not our aim.
What does rest after saying the truth?
If you are real, I am a lie.
A paradise without angels!
# The curse of the devil is in the songs
# filled by enthousiasm my
situation is serious
# This game is always bad. My dices
always are marked
# It is the endless game, that is
played by fate
# If the dices fall in this way
# I use to love the beautiful but they
have to be young
# The heart is incorrigible
Look at Hoca and Tatu!
They are having fun.
Let them enjoy themselves.
Why did you come here?
What did you do?
The ambience is very good. Will I let
dance Halay?
No, wait! Delay what you can.
Go on until they become red.
Ferhat, wo do you stay?
- All are waiting for you!
- I am no more of the game.
- What does this mean?
- I am not of the game.
- Come and rise!
- No, let me. Why are you here?
Because of this money. If I could
get some of it...
I will buy a ticket to my country.
This guy really does want to become slim.
Look at this! All personalities
of the world of records and newspapers
have come.
- But where is this little bastard?
- Take it easy and sit down.
This person always has depressions.
What for?
As if his beloved has been fucked.
This damned, stupid german!
- Go, Ferhat.
- Give up me, Melih!
Why do you give up this dream?
It is because a girl, isn't it?
- Why not?
- I also am in love.
Therefor I can't sing there now.
- Who is she, man?
- Melek.
Melek?
It is her wedding.
- How are you? -You are honouring us.
Thank you very much!
Tayyar will kill us. Who is acting
in stead of Ferhat?
No. Studio yes. I am no type for stage.
Will we get off with the money?
In taht case we are lost...
Who was it?
Go well.
There are no problems, are there?
- No problems. Everything goes digitally!
- Flowers!
- Look, what I have for you.
- What's that?
My bill. Tayyar gave me the advance.
You have to pay the musicians with the rest.
You beggars.
Tayyar will present you an account also.
I didn't want to say it, but the musicians get
their money from another source.
- That's not true!
- It is. I got the rest in cheque.
- Tayyar does understand you.
- Where is the artist?
Without money no artist.
You have to know it.
The son of the "heel-killer" wants to marry
and you leave the wedding-party.
Gratulations, you have courage.
- Do you pay at least value added tax?
- Don't worry, we will fix it.
They shoot, if we stay.
But also, if we try to flee.
We have a umbrella inside.
And they have opened it.
The movie has ended. But they don't write
"end".
You have to see it.
- What is the matter?
- What kind of movie?
Ýbrahim und Sansar put the money
in their pocket
and didn't pay the orchestra. We are lost.
It is all right! An entry at this wedding
wouldn't be suitable to you!
It would not be suitable to you also.
Fortunately we have no entry!
- Do you know, why we are loosing?
- Why?
Why we are capitulating always?
Because we always, we always...
- How?
- Why?
- We are to honest!
- Humbug!
Really.
It is true.
It is softening you up finally.
- I have been softened up.
- Yes, it softens you up.
You have to take it easy sometimes.
Cheers? I would kill the person,
who has served me this serum, in the
middle of Taksim-square.
Stop it, Seyfi.
He makes me furious!
Melih,
we should let it be.
You are wright.
If we are already on our way...
- If we suicide...
- We do it living.
# Forgive me
# It is too early for loosing and too late for
loving
# Forgive me
Sir Tayyar
Forbidden, I let if forbid in Turkeye and now
he is acting on my party!
# At least your name should remain at the
end of broken things
# Pursued by Lonelyness
# Forgive me
# At time of my love
# There still has been rain in this city
Kill the bastard!
# Forgive me
# It is too early for loosing
# And too late for loving
# Forgive me
# At time of my love
# There still has been rain in this city
# Love was as heavy as led in this city
# Forgive me
# The poems of your eyes
# The songs of your hair
Did you really want to kill me or not?
Death is the end of all suffering.
We are on earth in order
to make suffering so that hell can be
unburdened.
- Wag, you are really sensitive!
- Yes very.
That is a part of my profession.
Sometimes feelings are stronger than
reason.
Let us make a box for you.
That was only a joke!
Here a demo. Listen to it!
- I will apply to you.
- Of course you will.
- Certainly I will apply.
- So do it!
- I did say it, haven't I?
- Yes, you will excuse me now.
- What's the matter?
- We will throw out you immediately.
That's how the profession is like.
We will break one or two of your
bones also. By tradition.
Do you prefer some of them?
Properly we prefer an existing bone
Orhan, flee!
What do you look? Get them!
# There is no return. I have put fire
to all my ships
# This masked ball with all these false
# faces is unbearable to me
One mosque is not enough to you, uncle?
Let us go.
Let us save them.
You believe, it is a fire?
Is the basis ready?
All ready, in remembrance to our
common nights.
Wait! Firuze, where are you?
Ferhat has found Firuze.
Don't believe, that it is the end.
The endless competition never will stop.
They will weep a lot about us and they will
laugh.
Now all together.
# Starving melodies are snaring my heart
# Such a dream, as there were merely songs
# Flying birds seagulls
# A sweet and green springtime
# Laughing and merry love-pairs
# Here were sorrows, there desires
# Such a sea of loving waves
I have token everything from hospital.
I don't want to come with you now.
Everybody should decide for himself.
No, impossible.
We have begun together
and we will end together.
It is better, that he doesn't know, that he
has a poor father.
It doesn't mind, that I will not be there.
I am a burden.
He should throw me off.
It is the end for me but I am sorry, that
I have put you with me.
That's not necessary! Cheers!
Now the end has come finally.
Sorry, I haven't succeeded.
Sorry, I have a gastric ulcer.
They have gone!
- Seyfi?
- Melih!
Ferhat?
- Ferhat, wake up, my boy.
- I beg you!
We are loosing him! Run, keep water.
Please, come!
Ferhat, wake up.
- You coward!
- Where is Firuze?
We have been reborn.
Friends, let us start at zero again.
Nobody can halt us.
We will found a new company with
a colourful name.
The turn is on us, to serve electric shocks
like the fish under the sand.
What was his name?
RA- RAY!
To Hilmi Topaloglu.
Scandal at the wedding!
Their album has been sold 2 million copies.
Turkey is talking about them.
"I was a lighter, I became a director. Now it's
Hollywood!"
We all owe it to Firuze.
Melek broke up with her lover.
Firuze still at large.