To my brother Mehmet, who always
wanted me to shoot a Turkish film.
Groaning melodies entered into my soul.
Such a dream is a place of eternal songs.
Singers and
loving people everywhere.
The music world is like
dreams, like an own world.
Everybody wants to become a singer, wants
to get famous and honoured, but...
...all people are waiting for agenerous
stranger, for a saving angel, who...
...is taking them by hand.
They are waiting for us.
Hear, the time has come.
As there are policemen in civil...
...there are angels in civil, who are
living here.
this film was inspired by true stories
They have composed songs, even
have asked for help.
A visit without invitation is not
suitable for the race...
of angels that much caprice is necessary.
Properly everything there
is like a movie.
If you are open for such things, it will be
impossible to you...
...to distinguish reality of movie...
It is like a tale.
Everywhere evil wolfs are leering.
Well, there is Seyfi...
...he is the leader of the group. He is an
artist, who knows his profession:
The first setting of the movie is the most
important one.
If this is correct your spectator will be
bound.
His glance will be tied
like the eyes of a duck
...that is looking at a fish.
Like a confused duck.
The main point of shooting
is the position of the camera.
Give it to me! Hurry up, we want to
record right now.
Move don't look like fishes, who have
seen a duck! Music!
What kind of music? Do you have
something to do with music?
I was a fan of Elvis.
In former days I listened to jazz.
When I was in love...
...I liked Arabic music and than rock.
I prefer arrangements, like flowers.
Now treason and injustice reign the
music world.
Good people exist only in tales.
An example: love had robbed all reason
of Melih...
...a promising young singer.
He also was one of these people...
...who would sacrifice
everything for love.
Who is left will be my haul.
Where is my red-brown crane?
Why didn't you get changed?
I will not act. I have come in order to collect
my luggage.
Where to? With this guy?
Didn't I say you, that he is not allowed to
show himself at this place?
Get away you!
That's the reason, that he is waiting outside.
Tayyar, I have to get money still!
First the scene, than the money!
Where can I find a singer still?
I am pregnant. I need the money.
What, you are pregnant?
No stage to ya no more Melih! You'll
sing in bath houses only!
Don't cry so loudly! You don't know
anything!
Give me the money, you arse-hole!
You can't call a Lacen an arse-hole
without loosing your life...
Why without consequences?
The angels are surrounding her but
sometimes unexpected things happen.
Suddenly all doors had been closed to them.
They didn't see any exit.
An awkward love-fairy
There was this nice saying
played a bad game with these lost souls.
They all fall together, if one of
them is falling.
We couldn't permit it.
Did somebody make promises?
The financial decisions have been
made at the last meeting.
- That's not important.
- With whom has been arranged this?
Mister Orhan,
a genius in financing. Specialist for legal
contracts.
He has succeeded to make a warm
refuge of a tiny hotel-room.
One is appealing for prayer. Please get up!
The prayer, Orhan Abi!
Hoca would like it to have a talk with
you. The debts are towering up.
He is downstairs and seems to
be very upset.
Okay, therefore I have woken up early.
After the prayer I wanted...
You didn't still sign a contract, did you?
He have made an usual agreement
with the producer.
Hayri Bey is a remarkable head.
He is really charismatic.
He is worried about his artists
like a protecting fairy.
They will come soon.
Oh god, let it go well!
Stop it, so early in the morning!
Let me go to the W.C, you son of a bitch!
It is not easy, to produce music.
Mister Hayri feels a peculiar pleasure
at the meal of the wolfs.
They find a diamant in the mud.
His career has begun in Europe.
He advanced quickly.
Now we are at Love!
Sure, a honourable boy, but a certain
distance is necessary.
A real cuddle-cat!
Come and applaud also!
Enough! Pigs!
St, the boss is calling!
You are terrific, applaud with us!
- Hello, I am Sansar.
- I know you.
Tonight there will be a Turkish night in
Munich.
I would like to be the star on the stage
in stead of Erdil.
- Don't you havea manager?
- No.
Such a coincidence!
You have to sign here! In Germany
nothing works without contract.
Whom do I see?
Coming all the way to here!
- He is it!- Friends, we have to interrupt
the meeting. There is a visitor.
Welcome.
Please be quite, madam Firuze.
Excuse me, can we have a talk outside?
This person is seeking me everywhere!
# Stay, where you are
# Don't make me crazy
# I haven't to pay a bill
# neither have I to go to confession
# I don't see my left hand, not my right hand
# I can't separate friends of enemies
# I don't know myself anymore.
I capitulate and stop the game
- How are you, Hayri?
- Wow! Is there somebody at the door?
See you!
You damned... That's my house.
You can't exchange the lock!
Asshole!
Please, open the door.
- Otherwise I will break it open!
- Shut up!
Don't shout! Open that damned door!
I only want to Change my clothes and
will go again immediately.
Show me the children!
You have forgotten, how our children
look like.
- I am getting crazy! That's my house!
- The bum of that bitch is your home.
Your companions are not able also to
maintain their wives.
I look after the woman here.
I will say to Seyfi, that he has to pick up me.
We have discovered a new voice.
The boy is great.
A voice like candy. The new Pavarotti.
We will make studio-sessions today.
Not with the same clothes.
Neval, I will dedicate you the album.
- Piss off!
- What is the matter, Neval?
- Hamit!
- Good morning.
- How are you, my love?
- Good, but I hardly can hear you.
- Take off your headphones!
- I don't hear anything.
Regard this face, this attitude. The people
will close him in their hearts.
The people will close me in their hearts.
- Hopefully everything is going well today.
- Thanks.
- I would wish, that you will stay modest
always. Okay? -I will not Change.
- No, not at all. What's the matter with
the basis? -Everything is clear:
the violins and the percussion. -Did
the scoundrels play well? -Excellent!
Come with us. Welcome on the market
of records, Hamit.
Look around very well.
Here is the real battle-field.
If you enter here by foot, your heart
will beat wildly.
- What is that? - A pump.
- A natural injection.
- A natural injection-pump. -That's why you
have to appear here with a safe tank
so that the rifles of the infantry immediately.
Hayri, do you know, which datum we have?
- You have to talk with him.
- But he is totally silly already.
- What do you drink?
- Medicine for nightingales.
- What is this supposed to be?
- It makes singing every silent nightingale.
Hayri wants studio-fee.
I hardly could Change his mind.
- Let's work now.
- Thanks.
Music.
The tape has a rotation-problem. It is turning
round too quickly.
- No, Ahmet Bey did want this way.
- Who is Ahmet Bey?
And we have been in accordance of his
wishes. Several times we have said to him.
- One moment, dear Ahmet.
- Yes, please?
You know, that the record has cost the
whole money. The musicians have arrived.
The pit is in a way too sharp.
How do you mean being able to sing this?
- I have prepared explicitly B-flat. I am tenor.
- What?
B- flat.
Hayri, I am the king.
Well, we will see!
You and B-flat, you fucked nightingale!
The A is better for you.
- We have to edit it.
- Go away with lukewarm water.
No, I mean the cassette tape. But how
and with whom?
- We have to find somebody, Hayri?
- What?
So we went to bottom totally.
- Is not there a fish, that is living at the bottom? What is his name?
- How can I know it?
Such a flat one with prickles on his tail.
I know, that poisonous one.
He serves electric shocks. We are like them.
We are laying in the sand and waiting
noiseless.
Suddenly we attack.
No, we don't want to get a shock.
Look, if the tape of Ýbrahim Tatlýses doesn't
arrive, could...
...you give him back the box and
request your money?
We are not able to sell it. We are
still sitting on it.
Friends, the music-family of Umut remotes the
word repayment out of his vocabulary right now.
- Our possibilities for retaking are tired out.
- What does it mean?
It is limited at 30%, but we haven't even
made al 50% of the music-box.
Go, my friend!
Go, my friend.
Ýbrahim's bull!
That's the matter, master?
Who is coming there? Welcome, my dear!
I just have said to the boys,
that Ibrahim is looking like Elvis very
much! Haven't I, Orhan? -Yes, you have.
Orhan, my dear, you have sold the not
existing tape except to me to otherpeople.
Orhan, coffee. That are all rumours!
You are our marketing man.
Oh no! How do you want to pay?
Well, this new boy, what was his name? He
is tenor, singing B-flat, believe me!
What does B-flat mean? Could you sell
his last tape?
Not at all! Nothing happened.
We have made 15000 records of his last
box but we had to retake 25000.
Even the boxes of the black market had
been burdened to us.
Tayyar, my sir, we just have
spoken about you.
Twenty days?
That never will be sufficient! Say it to me, if I
make a mistake.
Your debts amount to 88.000 $
I beg you, say at least twenty days!
Say it to me, if I make a mistake.
What will we do, Hayri?
We will go to sleep three times and will
wake up three times.
After three days we will get our
money or not?
What will be now? Boxes mean money.
We let sing somebody, but whom?
Well, I get a little bit money...
...of the last box. I have thought: if it is
convenient now...
Hayri?
Orhan?
Why do you laugh?
You have broken the nose of
a new singer!
- No, I don't have people for you.
- This Sansar was not able to sing the song.
One can't beat up all people
who are not able to sing.
In short time you would have a
slaughterhouse.
Honoured audience, the unique national
634th competition...
...for the golden dream presents participant
number 42: Semra Comez!
- We have no other merchandise for you.
- Sansar,
we want this boy from Germany.
No, if I bring him here, he may have
money...
...that will land in your pocket.
You will produce
the box for good money...
...and my fee will be a watch.
No, my love, I can't do anything for you.
Ferhat, that you had to call me.
I was not present just at the moment, you
wanted to telephone me.
Something is wrong with the international
connections. I could not reach you.
How is the weather in Germany?
Well, my friends tell me that I look very
well, but you might have your own opinion.
Please? No, my eyebrows did not grow
together...
...but if you want, I can let them grow.
That's what they do themselves already.
Therefor I meant... rap, pop, jazz, I could
sing everything.
Ferhat, sing something!
In B-flat please!
That's a serious supply for a box, isn't it?
# I am a male old maid
# There is no wife for
lazy-bones
# What can we make still?
# I am not able to rob a bank
# In that way I have come to love
# My love is totally different
# I have seen so many beautiful girls.
The whole day
# Men do suffer also and not so little
# but this is no solution. Only the matrimony
gives purification
Ýbrahim, my record-master has to come and
edit my box...
...otherwise I will suicide.
Make for me a box! Than I will
become famous.
Hear, daddy, let me explain. Please, let me
explain it.
Tayyar sends you his greetings.
Stop! Nothing may be wrong left or right?
Where is Umut-music, please?
Left.
Oh, my god! They kill!
Allah, Allah!
- Master, they have killed somebody inside.
- All life will be taste dead. - What?
- They have shot Ibrahim!
- Salvation to your soul, Ýbrahim!
- They have hit his heel only! -Could you
save your life again, you dirty swine!
- Where is Umut-music?
- Look over there.
But in reality there is no hope and no music.
If you can wait, you may meet her.
I repeat, we will pay. Orhan, do something!
I can't do anything, I am standing
between two liquidations.
Hayri, let it be! Let it be their blame!
Forget it!
Let me the little T.V. please. Tomorrow
comes an international game. Osman!
You are on my black list, because you
have done this to me.
Cancel that list, man!
Rather pay your debts.
- Hayri!
- Good recovery, my dear Ibrahim!
- That has nothing to do with us.
You have still two days, do you understand?
I am lost. They take even the fax.
Please not! Be pity!
Please not! Not the fax!
You can take evrything, everything!
They will kill me,if they discover, that I have
bought it in a second hand shop.
How much did you pay for it, my little boy?
What kind of money? I have paid with
natural products.
Three parcels with dance-music!
Your name should be engraved in the
monument for the resurrected people.
Your are such a fox!
What do you say? The inner of the
TV was empty.
I have put a sewing-machine in it in order to
make it heavier.
- Really?
- Pardon, who is Mister Hayri?
- He has died, I regret.
- How?
- His mortal remains are
washed. - Has he died? - Yes.
What do you say there? It is for him, that
I have made such a long voyage.
- Who is seeking him?
- Ferhat Can from Germany.
My hero, dear brother, Hayri!
Welcome, you well-looking star.
Let us beat the record at the record-market.
Orhan,
call for the notary in order to make a
protocol.
A record in short time producing of
music-boxes!
Orhan, call now for the studio in
order to record.
Not now, it is closed. To-morrow.
OK, OK, to-morrow.
So you have time for learning the songs.
Everything here in Istanbul goes fast.
- There is my partner Orhan.
Where is Seyfi? - Hello!
Clip PR-leader Seyfi. You know already
our star Melih.
Well, that TV...
Do make something. Well, we were busy,
we wanted to renew the decorations...
...and than you came. Excuse me for the
disorder.
Come to here. This here and this.
- Is it ready?
- Yes, ready. That is it!
What kind of market is this? I thought,
you were dead.
God save us! He might give us all a long life.
Ferhat there is this fish, that is hiding
under the sand.
If you step on him he offers you an
electric shock.
That's what I want to ask you the whole
time, but I am forgetting it ever.
We are exactly like this fisch.
We will strike, Melih.
Bring him to Kahtalý in order to tidy up.
With this hair he has no chance.
Let us cut it.
This boy will become very famous.
We will strike.
It will come a day, that we enter this hotel
with pride and high breast.
That is it! Tatu Head&Leg is
presenting proudly.
- Do you need something more?
- Bring another bottle. Will we drink it?
Delicious. I haven't eaten it since
three months.
- Orhan, what did we properly sign today?
- A contract.
Sansar let me sign something also.
Let me see!
Miss Sansar is really okay.
We make charges and PR and she gets
the whipped cream.
It does go like that! Here is a paragraph, that
binds you ten years at us.
- What, ten years?
- Well, than good luck!
What do you think?
Last five years I am not able to think of other
things than of music.
Sometimes your look is darkling.
Nevertheless you are going on. Than you
look back and you see,
that you are at the same place.
You are not there.
- Hopefully this room will bring you
good luck. - Hopefully.
It didn't bring me luck, but I am content,
when I am in love.
We are artists. We are living of air and love.
I repeat it many times. This boy is so
sensitive.
I beg you pardon, my nerves!
- Because you have said...
- Boy to a full-grown man.
- What is the connection with your baby?
- High blood pressure.
It would be better, if she doesn't
get her baby.
The results of the medical
examination are bad.
That is the revenge of the sensitive people.
We are lost.
Does somebody come with me
into the night-bar?
# There is no kind of sorrows, that I don't
know, that I didn't suffer
# No day, no night without grief
After the black-out of current he jumped
to the stage.
He has a good voice but no reason. Right
away he has contacted Tayyar.
- Who is Tayyar?
- Come, my egg, please come!
Hayri, you have brought bad
luck to this girl!
The one, who let shoot in the foot of
Ýbrahim, is Tayyar
- Why did he do it?
- Main point is...
...the length of the prick, do you understand?
We have found a job at Kumkapý.
Tayyar has forbidden Melih, to go on stage.
He let shoot in the leg of the operator
of the club.
But why got Melih upset?
Tayyar has fallen in love with Melih's girl.
That the reason, why his behaviour is gentle.
# There is no trace of my old ego
# I am tired of the pains
# Please support my arms.
Otherwise I will fall down
# I am so lonesome and lonely
Why don't you tell this guy, that you are
pregnant?
He doesn't know, if he will marry me.
There is still time.
What ever will happen, I will give
birth to this baby.
First time of my life I am doing
something useful.
Let us say, that we tolerate these men
because of their victorious future.
If their luck has turned and the money is
flowing...
...they will leave us.
The truth is, girls, that there are only roles
for men in this picture.
What will happen with us?
My dear god, why did you create these
women?
# I don't like it any more
# To be playthings!
# Am I a slave?
# So delivered I am tired of life
# She can go, if she doesn't need
me any more
# Give me patience...
Here is the real battle-field.
We will win.
Kahtalý! We will record.
He is really a nighintale.
My hero, my best one!
Did I succeed?
- Do I have a box also?
- Come and let me kiss you! Well made!
What have I said you?
This boy will belong to the very grand
people, I promise.
What is the matter here?
We have discovered him and you will pick
him up! No sir!
Didn't you want to come to me directly
after your arrival?
Don't exaggerate it, Sansar!
The last one, you have served us, was suited
to nothing. Thereafter we took that one.
To where, what is the matter? No, there is
nothing, to where do you go?
One minute.
Here is a copy of the contract and
what do we read?
Ferhat Can, living at Berlin,
Neuköllnstr. 62.
Bravo, you gained the rights.
The German judges will worry about them.
Well, perhaps it will make sense,
if you ask my advice...
...before making the next contract, Sansar.
This here has not ended!
There comes an aftermath.
Sansar, will never forget this.
She will not forget it! She is an elephant.
What, twenty?
In spite of your debts I have to spend
my own money for...
...t Do you have more wishes? s?
You have to trust me, Osman!
You know, my name means confidence.
What kind of confidence?
The loss of your TV by decision
of the court?
Japanese technology is great.
Look, the new mobile phone is...
...a flat-iron at the same time.
- Really?
We will buy it for your wife.
# Don't trust him with your love
# He will transform your tears to ferocious
streams
# Thanks to men your laughing will become
weeping
# Don't be deceived by him, don't
believe him
# He will leave you and will
speak about you
# He will leave you and will speak
about you
Stop it!
The face of the black man is too dark!
Good! But what will we do?
With more light she will look shabby,
with less light...
...the black dancer will be in darkness.
What can we do?
How do the Americans succeed?
They have black, red, white and mixed
people?
The Americans do know their business.
So Tanju Gürsoy doesn't want to
participate on our program.
You don't still have the demo of that boy.
He also looks very well. Could you
take charge of him?
I will give birth to this child, whatever it will
cost me.
You will guard me and my child.
Muammer!
What the hell is this?
Sterling from North-Africa!
In which pocket can I put this stuff?
It has been written in the contract, that the
rent is paid in foreign currency.
Well, that is exactly what we are doing.
In the exchange office they have regarded the card,
but didn't even find the name of the country, my child.
Surely it was an obsolete card.
Now they have new ones, after civil war...
...many people have died. Didn't you
hear about it?
They have gold-leads.
Look, the nephew of this king has given
us the money personally.
We make a box for his nephew. Heaven,
what a voice!
- A nightingale!
- Heaven, we will become rich.
I have enough of you. You have to leave
this shop immediately, understood?
Run!
If we don't organise money for the...
...advertisements of the box, we will be lost.
Do you call it black money?
# My breath suffices to say it
# but what, if you don't listen to me?
# I have come in order to proceed
through the sea of love
# and to plunge into your ocean
# I am the better creature of god
# have no bad veins
# I am the nightingale of these company
# I have come to you in order to sing for you
# My deficit is my kernel
# I have come for living in your home
Hayri! Osman didn't make the boxes!Shit!
Osman, you breach of promise!
I will kill you! Go away!
Hayri, I beg you, stop it!
You got that much money. Don't you
have any conscience?
I beg you pardon, take it as repayment
of your former debts.
Without a brother like you I would do
much better!
And you, brother? Because of you
I was even in prison!
Only one week! There are people who
use to die for their brothers.
You kill your brother with your own hands!
- If mother would be still alive, she would
spit you in your face! -Mama!
- What do you say there, are you crazy?
- Let the family out of game.
You have blamed us enough already.
Gods punishment will strike you!
- Damned the day, where on I became your
brother! -It is you, who should be damned!
- I said it first! - Damned!
- I took green.
- 572 €
- Is the plot inclusive?
I am so sorry, but
the medicines from Germany are
transported in...
...little condensers. Therefore they are a
little bit expensive!
I have to stay culpable for the half.
How much is an €, most honoured man?
I say hello!
- Looks great!
- Money!
Look at him!
"Nice clothes. Take them off. Come with
me to my home".
- Hayri!
- Already one time more! Come separate!
We have been saved!
Didn't I say you, that I will take revenge for
you and Neval.
This day has come.
- What do you say there?
- Didn't Tanju Gürsoy cancel?
Therefore they bring out young talents.
I have given the demo to the
stage-assistent.
I have said, that he possesses
evening-clothes also.
Well. But Osman didn't make the boxes
if Ýbrahim hears it, he will make us to
ground meat!
If Ferhat wins the friendship of
Ýbrahim at TV?
If he says, that he has supported him?
In that case we will be saved?
Promotion, TV, I got you, Ýbrahim!
- Come, go now! When is the broadcasting?
- It is urgent, immediately!
Do you have your clothes with you?
- Well, I used the money of the
advertisements for... - OK, Melih,
go quickly to the hotel and take it.
Well Orhan, let us tell it Ýbrahim
"Nice clothes. Take them off. Baby,
come with me to my home. "
Hear, give me the key of Ferhat's
hotelroom!
I really thought, it was the old uncle,
Isn't that Ferhat's stage-costume,
that you wear?
Right. Exactly!
- What did you do?
- I modified it. It will be my stage-costume...
Oh, no! What did you do?
Ferhat, how are you looking?
What is the matter?
Seyfi, the studio is waiting for you.
Go! Hurry up!
The humorists to this side and the
singers to the other one.
Say: "My biography has begun very sad.
Everybody died already, when
I was still very little"
- Improvise something!
- And if it will come to light later?
Than you can say, that they have
died for you.
Don't forget, to bring the audience to
applause...
...move your head a little bit to the right at
the beginning of the song!
- Go! - We come! Give him the stuff
afterward, when he goes.
- What stuff?
- Not before the end of singing.
You wait here and than you will
be called in series.
- She is really like an angel.
- Her name is Melek
- That's not true!
- It is. You are in love, don't you?
I am dying, man!
Look Ferhat, when the red light is burning...
...the camera will be pointed at you, okay?
- Regard my artists!
Hello, make everything well. They are my
artists!
Don't take me with you as if I were a
pimp.
How often I did explain it to you?
My car was defect.
You didn't do me a pleasure. Besides we
haven't made an agreement,
that you would come to me in my home.
But it has happened. So I can see,
where you are living.
- Can I do something goods to you?
- What do you mean?
- Will I give you the telephone-number?
- Of whom?
Okay, let me do it!
I love fashion shows.
The only thing, that I don't like, are the
clothes.
Underwear is not the worst thing.
- Nature would be better.
- Hayri?
- Yes, my dear? -Do you know, why she
has shot me in my foot?
I know, it handled of the prick-length.
- Ss!
- What? What did you say?
- Why?
-20000 Hayri!
I want the boxes and the money.
To-morrow is deadline.
You will be amazed, they will bring our new
boy now instead of...
...Tanju Gürsoy, isn't it, Orhan?
- Solo, solo!
Money!
Damned, in spite of my illness they brought
me to here! I am there!
Welcome.
Don't smile to me like a queen
of wines, my child.
Look, I have come to here in spite of illness
without bribery I will not act.
Now we are sitting in the shit!
Sorry, we have to modify the broadcast.
Well, next time better!
- Oh, no!
- In this way it will not go. Go now!
Welcome, dear spectators at the screen.
You do know him from his pictures,
his songs,
his private style of life and his
terrific shows.
Bravo, thist time you have founf somebody,
who is really good.
- I have notion of talents.
- For you: Tanju Gürsoy!
Your whole life is a lie!
So I came in spite ofillness.
I was longing for my fans.
Welcome. Straight on:
One is asking if there is silicon in this
terrific body?
In my boby everything is natural. As I said
already:
I am totally content about myself.
Isn't this answer worth for an applause?
One knows her because of her famous days.
But how were the years at the conservatory?
Surely, the voice has become
a little bit worse.
Education is very important.
I have learned at two universities.
I studied at the medical faculty of Çapa.
Neuro-psychology.
After some years at the university I was
snared by my passion for music.
We have had good, important teachers.
We were taught loving, important...
...pots boiling with love and passion.
My teacher brought me into a concert.
After some vocal problems of the soloist
he threw me on the stage!
What is this?
Is it a joke?
Do you see it!
My artist is at T.V.!
He is the coming star on the market.
- My name is Ferhat.
- Very fine.
- My family-name is Can.
- What did he say?
He still didn't say anything!
We have made an album for Umut Müzik
with friends.
He said Umut Müzik!
The album is called "Flowerfields".
What happened? The current!
He did want to thank you at this way:
"We are editing the box thanks Ýbrahim"
Bring the generator!
If you ask me now, what music means, so...
Let us ask, otherwise he will die by
excitement.
Well, music means to me a beautiful woman,
as beautiful as you.
I go to bed with her and wake up with her.
I wish you a good broadcast. What is this,
where is Art staying?
That is more like a erotic broadcast. Say,
there is a woman in me.
Ask and give the answer yourself. What am I
seeking here?
That's Tanju Gürsoy!
You never know, how you are.
But if you would ask me, what Art is...
Do you ask me, what Art is?
Is there a generator?
In my opinion Art is a deal with the
spectator.
Properly all spectators are like one person.
You force them to listen and imagine,
that one of them at the screen is
recording you.
That is trade!
Now I have got the idea,
that I want to remember me to Ibrahim,
who truly accompanied me on these journey.
We thank you for this interesting
conversation and
continue our broadcast according
to the program.
There is a pause for advertising, but first...
# I was naiv and had been deceived
by the colour of the world
# I trusted a dream and was
despaired in vain
# I believed you would be mine for all times
# I am dying, beloved, and
you are my poison
# You were the first man in my life:
now you are the last
A generator, man! I give the Umut
music empire for a generator!
# I am a poor maiden, didn't do any
evil in this world
# I have established me in your
neighbourhood
# I never have confessed my love to
somebody
You are there still. What a scandal!
My poor heart!
Three minutes pause for advertising.
We are in advertising, 3.40.
# You are my centre and my cover
# My past and my last
Didn't we want to strike like that fish!
If there comes a storm, the fishes
will strike us.
Oh, if we could die now! We would be
free of this damned world!
Why don't you open it?
What do you make there?
- Here, the suicide-letter.
- Do you write often?
When inspiration comes,
sometimes.
- Read it to me!
- No, no! It is to absurd.
Well, read it!
- This is the suicide-letter of an
still existing Ferhat. -Go on!
Nobody is responsiblefor my death,
Ferhat Can.
- Hayri!
- This is not a despairing act.
- Really not? - Never before in my life
I felt so courageous.
I was in love with songs
I hope my tape will be published.
And my lifeless voice will be at stores.
This is my wish from Umut Music.
My soul will be with you.
Goodbye cruel world.
Goodbye.
Umut Müzik means everything for us.
Tomorrow it will be on all front pages.
All people will be baffled.
The letter is a poem. If this box will not be
sold like warm rolls, I let cut...
...my prick and become Hayriye.
Ferhat Can, represented by
Umut Music, stops with...
...the stolen car on the Bosporus bridge.
When he is holding his poetic...
...last letter in his hands, the camera
glides down very slowly...
...and falls. In this moment your song
begins, okay? -Everything is clear.
Some more effects...
...tears, a sincere, but bitter
smile on his face.
Than we will have succeeded.
- Who is playing too?
- Principe: best friend. Melih,...
You could play his role. Cry! Don't cry too
modestly.
You will return three months later. "Ferhat
Can, the box of Abi's ghost. "
Geistes Abi" It will be a big seller.
Thereafter we will celebrate in Russia.
- Did you sign the letter?
- What now?
The reader has to know, that it was you,
who had died.
I wrote it at the head of the letter.
There it is. It has be signed also. Even the
stamp of Umut Music has been given.
Bravo, well thought.
That is the wrong car! The letter ought
to be in the other car!
# Turkey Turkey you're a lovely country
# Turkey Turkey you're a cozy land.
# You're the land of chiskebab and raki
# You're the place of living I have planed
# Places full of very friendly people
# Always trying to help you if they can
# Turkey Turkey Turkey I adore you
# Turkey Turkey Turkey I love you
Ýbrahim? Hayri.
Let's make it short.
We were not able to organise money.
We are in the mud. We can't move us
above zero.
Two posters for 88000 $ 2 and one DAT.
Wonderful.
You want to cut out us?
What's on the box, that I could share?
If there is no other way to reach your mind:
we will send the bill and get the
money one day later.
There is no other way!
- Hello, Kaveci.
- How are you, daddy?
My foot?
Well, it sends you his greetings.
I did mind the bones. Good recovery!
Excuse for the circumstances. We are
mediators.
Of course, whatever you want.
Is it the bill, Hayri?
Enough! We don't chop off!
What does this mean?
We have to take the problem at the roots.
- Umut Music?
- Upstairs.
All people have their story. This one
will be our story.
Hello?
- Don't make humbug. Don't cause costs,
Hayri. - Say goodbye to my children.
- Umut Music, right?
- Yes?
I would like to buy a box
of Ferhat Can.
- In the moment we have no more boxes.
- And he?
- Who?
- Ferhat Can?
We don't have him either.
Probably he is walking
around a little.
- I hope, I didn't disturb your work.
- Not at all!
Go on, dear sirs, didn't you see something
like that never before?
We all are artists.
Kahtalý? Don't call the police!
It was the wrong shop. They thought,
it was Osman's one
and shot it.
- Go, go! - Where do you stay?
This lady is waiting for you.
He was in the hotel.
- Hello. I am Firuze.
- And I Ferhat.
Excuse me, there was a little accident.
Fortunately you haven't been injured.
Such a jewel as you are!
One should preserve you in worthy safes.
You have called me and I have come.
I am this person, who is pursuing you with
attentiveness.
I would like to have your box.
As you said: the selling has begin.
Are there boxes?
- Ferhat Bey, would you sing for me one
time more? - Of course.
What was it? " Come back "
is a beautiful song.
- Flowerfields.
- Really a beautiful song.
- Ferhats box is not ready.
- We have a momentary financial problem.
But mister Melih has beautiful boxes.
Thank you very much.
I would like to invest in you.
What do you mean?
I am well to do. My husband and I were
long times active for Art,
of course as dilettantes.
- Wonderful.
- Music is very important to me.
- And to your husband?
I lost him three years ago. Cancer.
My condolence...
What kind of cancer?
Heart-cancer, that means money.
Children, go out a moment.
I want to have a talk with this lady.
I wish, that mister Ferhat Bey
stays, please.
Of course he has to stay. I meaned...
There is no reason for secrets.
Ask for tea, if you want.
Our most urgent problem.
The financial problem can be solved easily.
Here is the bank.
We call for the director.
Hello, mister Altan.
Thank you.
Please, open for me an account,
favouring Ferhat Can.
He will be disposable to you for
informations. Speak!
Hello?
- Mother's name?
- Sýdýka.
- Father's name?
- Sinan.
- Where's your born?
- Ankara.
- Yours birth date?
- 76
Can I speak Miss Sýdýka again?
Thank you.
I want, that you will look very distinguished.
Hello Vakko?
Please write down his name:
Ferhat Can!
He comes to you for shopping.
Put everything on my meine account.
Thanks.
- Besides it looks untidily here. You have to
do something. -That is condition.
If you will make me happy, I will revenge me.
Do, what I say. The rest comes alone.
Main point you believe. See you soon!
Next time Secen will come with me.
She is able to give tips to you.
- Sezen?
- Sezen Aksu.
She was a narrow friend of my late husband.
- Once she composed a song for me.
- FÝRUZEE!...